{
  "uniqueId": "8",
  "showDictionaryLink": true,
  "name": "JLPT N2 Reading Quiz",
  "category": "JLPT",
  "article": "a",
  "instructions": "Type the reading of the below word in Hiragana!",
  "cards": [
    {"meaning":"pale,pallid","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"青白い","answer":["あおじろい"]},
    {"meaning":"room,time to spare,emptiness","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明き","answer":["あき"]},
    {"meaning":"dawn","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明け方","answer":["あけがた"]},
    {"meaning":"footprints","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"足跡","answer":["あしあと"]},
    {"meaning":"to taste,to savor,to relish","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"味わう","answer":["あじわう"]},
    {"meaning":"impudent,shameless,brazen","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"厚かましい","answer":["あつかましい"]},
    {"meaning":"to act violently,to rage,to struggle,to be riotous","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"暴れる","answer":["あばれる"]},
    {"meaning":"fat,tallow,lard","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"脂","answer":["あぶら"]},
    {"meaning":"sliding storm door","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"雨戸","answer":["あまど"]},
    {"meaning":"to pamper,to spoil","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"甘やかす","answer":["あまやかす"]},
    {"meaning":"to remain,to be left over,to be in excess,to be too many","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"余る","answer":["あまる"]},
    {"meaning":"knitting,web","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"編物","answer":["あみもの"]},
    {"meaning":"to knit","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"編む","answer":["あむ"]},
    {"meaning":"dangerous,critical,grave","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"危うい","answer":["あやうい"]},
    {"meaning":"rough,rude,wild","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"荒い","answer":["あらい"]},
    {"meaning":"to dispute,to argue,to be at variance,to compete","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"争う","answer":["あらそう"]},
    {"meaning":"another time,again,over again,anew,formally","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"改めて","answer":["あらためて"]},
    {"meaning":"to change,to alter,to reform,to revise","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"改める","answer":["あらためる"]},
    {"meaning":"to write,to publish","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"著す","answer":["あらわす"]},
    {"meaning":"grateful,thankful,welcome,appreciated,evoking gratitude","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"有難い","answer":["ありがたい"]},
    {"meaning":"to live,to be","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"在る","answer":["ある"]},
    {"meaning":"easy-going","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"安易","answer":["あんい"]},
    {"meaning":"to start talking,to speak,to tell,to propose,to suggest,to break the ice","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"言い出す","answer":["いいだす"]},
    {"meaning":"to tell,to tell on (someone),to order","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"言い付ける","answer":["いいつける"]},
    {"meaning":"vividly,lively","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"生き生き","answer":["いきいき"]},
    {"meaning":"childcare,nursing,upbringing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"育児","answer":["いくじ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) flower arrangement","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"生け花","answer":["いけばな"]},
    {"meaning":"after this,from now on,hereafter,thereafter","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"以後","answer":["いご"]},
    {"meaning":"on and after,hereafter,thereafter","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"以降","answer":["いこう"]},
    {"meaning":"brave,valiant,gallant,courageous","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"勇ましい","answer":["いさましい"]},
    {"meaning":"necessities of life (food, clothing, etc.)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"衣食住","answer":["いしょくじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"malicious,ill-tempered,unkind","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"意地悪","answer":["いじわる"]},
    {"meaning":"greater,more,further,still more","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一段と","answer":["いちだんと"]},
    {"meaning":"first class,top grade,foremost,top-notch","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一流","answer":["いちりゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"day before yesterday","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一昨日","answer":["おととい","いっさくじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"year before last","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一昨年","answer":["おととし","いっさくねん"]},
    {"meaning":"fixed,settled,definite","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一定","answer":["いってい","いちじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"moving,transfer,demise","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"移転","answer":["いてん"]},
    {"meaning":"container,case,receptacle","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"入れ物","answer":["いれもの"]},
    {"meaning":"gravity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引力","answer":["いんりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"garden shrubs,trees,potted plant","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"植木","answer":["うえき"]},
    {"meaning":"to float,to rise to surface,to come to mind","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"浮ぶ","answer":["うかぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"to float,to express,to look (sad, glad)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"浮かべる","answer":["うかべる"]},
    {"meaning":"to float,to become merry,to become loose","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"浮く","answer":["うく"]},
    {"meaning":"(hum) to hear,to be told,to know","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"承る","answer":["うけたまわる"]},
    {"meaning":"receipt","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受取","answer":["うけとり"]},
    {"meaning":"to take (be in) charge of","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受け持つ","answer":["うけもつ"]},
    {"meaning":"dim,gloomy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"薄暗い","answer":["うすぐらい"]},
    {"meaning":"to dilute,to water down","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"薄める","answer":["うすめる"]},
    {"meaning":"business meeting,previous arrangement,appointment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"打合せ","answer":["うちあわせ"]},
    {"meaning":"to deny,to negate,to contradict","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"打ち消す","answer":["うちけす"]},
    {"meaning":"to project,to reflect,to cast (shadow)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"映す","answer":["うつす"]},
    {"meaning":"to be photographed,to be projected","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"写る","answer":["うつる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be reflected,to harmonize with,to come out (photo)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"映る","answer":["うつる"]},
    {"meaning":"to bury,to fill up,to fill (a seat, a vacant position)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"埋める","answer":["うめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to show respect,to honour","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"敬う","answer":["うやまう"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn inside out,to turn (something) over","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"裏返す","answer":["うらがえす"]},
    {"meaning":"backdoor,rear entrance","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"裏口","answer":["うらぐち"]},
    {"meaning":"to forecast,to predict","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"占う","answer":["うらなう"]},
    {"meaning":"amount sold,proceeds","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"売上","answer":["うりあげ"]},
    {"meaning":"sold-out","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"売り切れ","answer":["うりきれ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be sold out","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"売り切れる","answer":["うりきれる"]},
    {"meaning":"sales","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"売行き","answer":["うれゆき"]},
    {"meaning":"canal,waterway","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"運河","answer":["うんが"]},
    {"meaning":"sentence in English","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"英文","answer":["えいぶん"]},
    {"meaning":"English-Japanese (e.g. dictionary)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"英和","answer":["えいわ"]},
    {"meaning":"liquid,fluid","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"液体","answer":["えきたい"]},
    {"meaning":"colors,paints","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"絵の具","answer":["えのぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"great,celebrated,eminent,terrible,awful,famous,remarkable,excellent","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"偉い","answer":["えらい"]},
    {"meaning":"horticulture,gardening","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"園芸","answer":["えんげい"]},
    {"meaning":"play (theatrical)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"演劇","answer":["えんげき"]},
    {"meaning":"circumference","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"円周","answer":["えんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"trip,hike,picnic","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遠足","answer":["えんそく"]},
    {"meaning":"extension,elongation,prolongation,lengthening","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"延長","answer":["えんちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"chimney","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"煙突","answer":["えんとつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to chase or run after someone,to run down,to pursue","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"追い掛ける","answer":["おいかける"]},
    {"meaning":"to pass (e.g. car),to outdistance,to outstrip","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"追い越す","answer":["おいこす"]},
    {"meaning":"princess","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"王女","answer":["おうじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"Europe and America,the West","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"欧米","answer":["おうべい"]},
    {"meaning":"main street","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"大通り","answer":["おおどおり"]},
    {"meaning":"return,welcome","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"お帰り","answer":["おかえり"]},
    {"meaning":"to worship,to beg,to make a supplication","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"拝む","answer":["おがむ"]},
    {"meaning":"second helping,another cup","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"お代わり","answer":["おかわり"]},
    {"meaning":"to compensate for","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"補う","answer":["おぎなう"]},
    {"meaning":"outdoors","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"屋外","answer":["おくがい"]},
    {"meaning":"to stop,to restrain,to seize,to repress,to suppress,to press down","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"押える","answer":["おさえる"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to govern,to manage,(2) to subdue","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"治める","answer":["おさめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be taught","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"教わる","answer":["おそわる"]},
    {"meaning":"to calm down,to settle down","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"落着く","answer":["おちつく"]},
    {"meaning":"font of purifying water placed at entrance of shrine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"御手洗","answer":["おてあらい"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お出掛け","answer":["おでかけ"]},
    {"meaning":"maid","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お手伝いさん","answer":["おてつだいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"lost property","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"落し物","answer":["おとしもの"]},
    {"meaning":"each,every,either,respectively,severally","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"各々","answer":["おのおの","それぞれ"]},
    {"meaning":"worship,shrine visit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お参り","answer":["おまいり"]},
    {"meaning":"unexpected,casual","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"思い掛けない","answer":["おもいがけない"]},
    {"meaning":"to be under impression that,to be convinced that","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"思い込む","answer":["おもいこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"思いっ切り","answer":["おもいっきり"]},
    {"meaning":"to think of,to hit upon","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"思い付く","answer":["おもいつく"]},
    {"meaning":"heavy,massive,serious","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"重たい","answer":["おもたい"]},
    {"meaning":"thumb","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"親指","answer":["おやゆび"]},
    {"meaning":"greenhouse","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"温室","answer":["おんしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"spa,hot spring,onsen","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"温泉","answer":["おんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"temperate zone","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"温帯","answer":["おんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"and Company,Messrs.","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"御中","answer":["おんちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"woman","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"女の人","answer":["おんなのひと"]},
    {"meaning":"shell,shellfish","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"貝","answer":["かい"]},
    {"meaning":"opening of a meeting","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"開会","answer":["かいかい"]},
    {"meaning":"meeting hall,assembly hall","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"会館","answer":["かいかん"]},
    {"meaning":"examination of tickets","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"改札","answer":["かいさつ"]},
    {"meaning":"breakup,dissolution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解散","answer":["かいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"sea bathing,seawater bath","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"海水浴","answer":["かいすいよく"]},
    {"meaning":"number of times,frequency","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回数","answer":["かいすう"]},
    {"meaning":"book of tickets","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"回数券","answer":["かいすうけん"]},
    {"meaning":"revision,amendment,alteration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"改正","answer":["かいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"good weather","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"快晴","answer":["かいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"explanation,commentary","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解説","answer":["かいせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) remodeling,(2) modding (comp)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"改造","answer":["かいぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"opening,open","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"開通","answer":["かいつう"]},
    {"meaning":"rotation,revolution,turning","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回転","answer":["かいてん"]},
    {"meaning":"answer,solution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解答","answer":["かいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"reply,answer","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回答","answer":["かいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"the outside,external","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"外部","answer":["がいぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"release,liberation,emancipation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解放","answer":["かいほう"]},
    {"meaning":"open,throw open,liberalization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"開放","answer":["かいほう"]},
    {"meaning":"ocean","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"海洋","answer":["かいよう"]},
    {"meaning":"to send back","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"帰す","answer":["かえす"]},
    {"meaning":"to exchange,to interchange,to substitute,to replace","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"代える","answer":["かえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to warp,to be warped,to curve","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"反る","answer":["かえる"]},
    {"meaning":"house,building","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"家屋","answer":["かおく"]},
    {"meaning":"to concern oneself in,to have to do with,to affect,to influence,to stick to (opinions)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"係わる","answer":["かかわる"]},
    {"meaning":"writing down,putting on record,recording,making a note of,registration (of mail)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"書留","answer":["かきとめ"]},
    {"meaning":"dictation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"書取","answer":["かきとり"]},
    {"meaning":"individual,each","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"各自","answer":["かくじ"]},
    {"meaning":"science,learning,scholarship","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"学術","answer":["がくじゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"every place,various places","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"各地","answer":["かくち"]},
    {"meaning":"angle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"角度","answer":["かくど"]},
    {"meaning":"year in school,grade in school","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"学年","answer":["がくねん"]},
    {"meaning":"department of a university,undergraduate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"学部","answer":["がくぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"exceptional","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"格別","answer":["かくべつ"]},
    {"meaning":"scholarship,knowledge,literary ability","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"学力","answer":["がくりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"multiplication","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"掛け算","answer":["かけざん"]},
    {"meaning":"a burner,origin of a fire","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"火口","answer":["かこう"]},
    {"meaning":"downward,descent,fall,drop,subsidence","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"下降","answer":["かこう"]},
    {"meaning":"to be piled up,lie on top of one another,overlap each other","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"重なる","answer":["かさなる","おもなる"]},
    {"meaning":"to pile up,to put something on another,to heap up,to add,to repeat","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"重ねる","answer":["かさねる"]},
    {"meaning":"volcano","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"火山","answer":["かざん"]},
    {"meaning":"lending,loaning","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"貸し出し","answer":["かしだし"]},
    {"meaning":"error,blunder,accident","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過失","answer":["かしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"fruit,nut,berry.","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"果実","answer":["かじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"room to let","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"貸間","answer":["かしま"]},
    {"meaning":"house for rent","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"貸家","answer":["かしや"]},
    {"meaning":"passage,place,point,part","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"個所","answer":["かしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"taxation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"課税","answer":["かぜい"]},
    {"meaning":"underline,underscore","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"下線","answer":["かせん"]},
    {"meaning":"acceleration","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"加速","answer":["かそく"]},
    {"meaning":"acceleration","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"加速度","answer":["かそくど"]},
    {"meaning":"stubborn,firm (not viscous or easily moved)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"固い","answer":["かたい"]},
    {"meaning":"to put in order,to dispose of,to solve","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"片付く","answer":["かたづく"]},
    {"meaning":"to harden,to solidify,to become firm,to become certain","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"固まる","answer":["かたまる"]},
    {"meaning":"one-way (trip)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"片道","answer":["かたみち"]},
    {"meaning":"to incline toward,to slant,to lurch","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"傾く","answer":["かたむく","かたぶく"]},
    {"meaning":"to be one-sided,to incline,to be partial","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"片寄る","answer":["かたよる"]},
    {"meaning":"study subject,course of study","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"学科","answer":["がっか"]},
    {"meaning":"scientific society,academic meeting","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"学会","answer":["がっかい"]},
    {"meaning":"to shoulder,to carry on shoulder","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"担ぐ","answer":["かつぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"printing type","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"活字","answer":["かつじ"]},
    {"meaning":"vitality,energy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"活力","answer":["かつりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"process","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過程","answer":["かてい"]},
    {"meaning":"course,curriculum","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"課程","answer":["かてい"]},
    {"meaning":"heating","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"加熱","answer":["かねつ"]},
    {"meaning":"majority","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過半数","answer":["かはんすう"]},
    {"meaning":"to cover (with something)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"被せる","answer":["かぶせる"]},
    {"meaning":"god","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"神様","answer":["かみさま"]},
    {"meaning":"cargo,freight","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"貨物","answer":["かもつ"]},
    {"meaning":"empty,vacant,hollow","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"空っぽ","answer":["からっぽ"]},
    {"meaning":"to wither,to die (plant),to be blasted (plant)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"枯れる","answer":["かれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to dry (clothes, etc.),to desiccate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乾かす","answer":["かわかす"]},
    {"meaning":"(v5r,vi) to take the place of,to relieve,to be substituted for","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"代る","answer":["かわる"]},
    {"meaning":"space,interval,SPC","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"間隔","answer":["かんかく"]},
    {"meaning":"ventilation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"換気","answer":["かんき"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"関西","answer":["かんさい"]},
    {"meaning":"to feel,to sense","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感ずる","answer":["かんずる"]},
    {"meaning":"indirection,indirectness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"間接","answer":["かんせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"dry,arid,insipid,dehydrated","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乾燥","answer":["かんそう"]},
    {"meaning":"impressions,thoughts","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感想","answer":["かんそう"]},
    {"meaning":"observation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"観測","answer":["かんそく"]},
    {"meaning":"frigid zone","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"寒帯","answer":["かんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"government office,authorities","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"官庁","answer":["かんちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"packing (in cans),canning,canned goods,tin can","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"缶詰","answer":["かんづめ"]},
    {"meaning":"dry cell,battery","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乾電池","answer":["かんでんち"]},
    {"meaning":"eastern half of Japan, including Tokyo","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"関東","answer":["かんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) idea,notion,conception,(2) sense (e.g. of duty)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"観念","answer":["かんねん"]},
    {"meaning":"toast (drink)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乾杯","answer":["かんぱい"]},
    {"meaning":"Chinese Character-Japanese (e.g. dictionary)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"漢和","answer":["かんわ"]},
    {"meaning":"atmospheric pressure","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"気圧","answer":["きあつ"]},
    {"meaning":"changing clothes,change of clothes","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"着替え","answer":["きがえ"]},
    {"meaning":"locomotive,engine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"機関車","answer":["きかんしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"term,period","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"期限","answer":["きげん"]},
    {"meaning":"symbol,code","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"記号","answer":["きごう"]},
    {"meaning":"to mince,to carve,to engrave","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"刻む","answer":["きざむ"]},
    {"meaning":"standard,basis,criteria,norm","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"規準","answer":["きじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"rising,getting out of bed","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"起床","answer":["きしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to put on clothes","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"着せる","answer":["きせる"]},
    {"meaning":"vapour,gas","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"気体","answer":["きたい"]},
    {"meaning":"guest seating","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"客席","answer":["きゃくせき"]},
    {"meaning":"parlor,guest room","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"客間","answer":["きゃくま"]},
    {"meaning":"closed (e.g. store),business suspended,shutdown,holiday","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"休業","answer":["きゅうぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"lecture cancelled","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"休講","answer":["きゅうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"rest,relief,relaxation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"休息","answer":["きゅうそく"]},
    {"meaning":"allowance,grant,supply","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"給与","answer":["きゅうよ"]},
    {"meaning":"rest,break,recreation","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"休養","answer":["きゅうよう"]},
    {"meaning":"clear,pure,noble","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"清い","answer":["きよい"]},
    {"meaning":"strengthen,intensify,reinforce,solidify","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"強化","answer":["きょうか"]},
    {"meaning":"boundary","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"境界","answer":["きょうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"event,function","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"行事","answer":["ぎょうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"culture,education,refinement,cultivation","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"教養","answer":["きょうよう"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) line,procession,(2) matrix (math)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"行列","answer":["ぎょうれつ"]},
    {"meaning":"fishing (industry)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"漁業","answer":["ぎょぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"curve","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"曲線","answer":["きょくせん"]},
    {"meaning":"order,rules,law","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"規律","answer":["きりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be careful,to pay attention,to take care","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"気を付ける","answer":["きをつける"]},
    {"meaning":"goldfish","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"金魚","answer":["きんぎょ"]},
    {"meaning":"limits,boundary,domain,zone,sphere,territory","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"区域","answer":["くいき"]},
    {"meaning":"even number","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"偶数","answer":["ぐうすう"]},
    {"meaning":"daydream,fantasy,fancy,vision","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"空想","answer":["くうそう"]},
    {"meaning":"sky,air","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"空中","answer":["くうちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to punctuate,to cut off,to mark off,to stop,to put an end to","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"区切る","answer":["くぎる"]},
    {"meaning":"complaint,troubles,objection","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦情","answer":["くじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"pain,trouble","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦心","answer":["くしん"]},
    {"meaning":"ring finger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"薬指","answer":["くすりゆび"]},
    {"meaning":"to get down,to descend","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"下る","answer":["さがる","くだる"]},
    {"meaning":"lipstick","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"口紅","answer":["くちべに"]},
    {"meaning":"to distribute,to deliver","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"配る","answer":["くばる"]},
    {"meaning":"labourer,worker","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"工夫","answer":["くふう"]},
    {"meaning":"combination","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"組合せ","answer":["くみあわせ"]},
    {"meaning":"to assemble,to set up,to construct","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"組み立てる","answer":["くみたてる"]},
    {"meaning":"honorific,term of respect","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"敬語","answer":["けいご"]},
    {"meaning":"form,formality,format,math expression","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"形式","answer":["けいしき"]},
    {"meaning":"knitting wool","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"毛糸","answer":["けいと"]},
    {"meaning":"longitude","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"経度","answer":["けいど"]},
    {"meaning":"public entertainment,accomplishments,attainments","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"芸能","answer":["げいのう"]},
    {"meaning":"horse racing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"競馬","answer":["けいば"]},
    {"meaning":"defense,guard,policing,security","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"警備","answer":["けいび"]},
    {"meaning":"true adjective","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"形容詞","answer":["けいようし"]},
    {"meaning":"adjectival noun,quasi-adjective","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"形容動詞","answer":["けいようどうし"]},
    {"meaning":"surgical department","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"外科","answer":["げか"]},
    {"meaning":"fur,skin,pelt","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"毛皮","answer":["けがわ"]},
    {"meaning":"alighting,getting off","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"下車","answer":["げしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"drainage,sewage,ditch,gutter,sewerage","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"下水","answer":["げすい"]},
    {"meaning":"geta (Japanese footwear),wooden clogs","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"下駄","answer":["げた"]},
    {"meaning":"blood pressure","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"血圧","answer":["けつあつ"]},
    {"meaning":"blood","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"血液","answer":["けつえき"]},
    {"meaning":"monthly salary","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"月給","answer":["げっきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"end of the month","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"月末","answer":["げつまつ"]},
    {"meaning":"indication,market trend,worry","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"気配","answer":["けはい","きはい"]},
    {"meaning":"vulgarity,meanness,indecency,coarseness","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"下品","answer":["げひん","かひん"]},
    {"meaning":"smoky","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"煙い","answer":["けむい"]},
    {"meaning":"inspection,study by observation,field trip","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"見学","answer":["けんがく"]},
    {"meaning":"place of origin,habitat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原産","answer":["げんさん"]},
    {"meaning":"origin,primeval","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原始","answer":["げんし"]},
    {"meaning":"prefectural office","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"県庁","answer":["けんちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"limit,bounds","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"限度","answer":["げんど"]},
    {"meaning":"actually,really","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現に","answer":["げんに"]},
    {"meaning":"principle,theory,fundamental truth","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原理","answer":["げんり"]},
    {"meaning":"raw materials","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原料","answer":["げんりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) dear,beloved,darling,(2) yearned for","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"恋しい","answer":["こいしい"]},
    {"meaning":"factory worker","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"工員","answer":["こういん"]},
    {"meaning":"overbearing,coercive,pushy,forcible,high-handed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"強引","answer":["ごういん"]},
    {"meaning":"public nuisance,pollution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公害","answer":["こうがい"]},
    {"meaning":"public,community,public service,society,communal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公共","answer":["こうきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"industrial arts","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"工芸","answer":["こうげい"]},
    {"meaning":"cross","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交差","answer":["こうさ"]},
    {"meaning":"lecturer","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"講師","answer":["こうし"]},
    {"meaning":"construction work","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"工事","answer":["こうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"formula,formality,official","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公式","answer":["こうしき"]},
    {"meaning":"excuse","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"口実","answer":["こうじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"perfume","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"香水","answer":["こうすい"]},
    {"meaning":"justice,fairness,impartiality","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"公正","answer":["こうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"beam,light ray","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"光線","answer":["こうせん"]},
    {"meaning":"upper","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"高層","answer":["こうそう"]},
    {"meaning":"structure,construction","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"構造","answer":["こうぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"alternation,change,relief,relay,shift","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"交替","answer":["こうたい"]},
    {"meaning":"arable land","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"耕地","answer":["こうち"]},
    {"meaning":"transportation facilities","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交通機関","answer":["こうつうきかん"]},
    {"meaning":"campus","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"校庭","answer":["こうてい"]},
    {"meaning":"positive,affirmation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"肯定","answer":["こうてい"]},
    {"meaning":"altitude,height,advanced","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"高度","answer":["こうど"]},
    {"meaning":"high class,high grade","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"高等","answer":["こうとう"]},
    {"meaning":"combination,incorporation,union,amalgamation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合同","answer":["ごうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"official announcement,proclamation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公表","answer":["こうひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"mineral","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"鉱物","answer":["こうぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"official business,public business","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公務","answer":["こうむ"]},
    {"meaning":"item","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"項目","answer":["こうもく"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) (Japanese) maple","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"紅葉","answer":["こうよう","もみじ"]},
    {"meaning":"rational","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合理","answer":["ごうり"]},
    {"meaning":"alternating current,intercourse,(cultural) exchange,intermingling","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交流","answer":["こうりゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"confluence,union,linking up,merge","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合流","answer":["ごうりゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"effect,efficacy,validity,potency","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"効力","answer":["こうりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"to exceed,to cross over,to cross","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"超える","answer":["こえる"]},
    {"meaning":"king","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"国王","answer":["こくおう"]},
    {"meaning":"nationality","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"国籍","answer":["こくせき"]},
    {"meaning":"national","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"国立","answer":["こくりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to freeze,to be chilled,to be frozen","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"凍える","answer":["こごえる"]},
    {"meaning":"having some knowledge of,happening to know","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"心当たり","answer":["こころあたり"]},
    {"meaning":"to be informed,to have thorough knowledge","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"心得る","answer":["こころえる"]},
    {"meaning":"seat,bench","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"腰掛け","answer":["こしかけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to sit (down)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"腰掛ける","answer":["こしかける"]},
    {"meaning":"the Japanese syllabary","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"五十音","answer":["ごじゅうおん"]},
    {"meaning":"to cross,to pass,to tide over","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"超す","answer":["こす"]},
    {"meaning":"an individual","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"個体","answer":["こたい"]},
    {"meaning":"feast,treating (someone)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"御馳走","answer":["ごちそう"]},
    {"meaning":"little finger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"小指","answer":["こゆび"]},
    {"meaning":"to roll","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"転がす","answer":["ころがす"]},
    {"meaning":"to roll,to tumble","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"転がる","answer":["ころがる"]},
    {"meaning":"mixing,mixture","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"混合","answer":["こんごう"]},
    {"meaning":"(enrolled) in school","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"在学","answer":["ざいがく"]},
    {"meaning":"again and again,repeatedly","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"再三","answer":["さいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"national holiday,festival day","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"祭日","answer":["さいじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"marking,grading,looking over","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"採点","answer":["さいてん"]},
    {"meaning":"lumber,timber","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"材木","answer":["ざいもく"]},
    {"meaning":"reverse,inversion,upside down","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"逆さ","answer":["さかさ"]},
    {"meaning":"inversion,upside down","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"逆さま","answer":["さかさま"]},
    {"meaning":"to search,to seek,to look for","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"捜す","answer":["さがす"]},
    {"meaning":"bar,bar-room","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"酒場","answer":["さかば"]},
    {"meaning":"some time ago","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"先程","answer":["さきほど"]},
    {"meaning":"author,authoress","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"作者","answer":["さくしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"frame,draw up,make,producing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"作成","answer":["さくせい"]},
    {"meaning":"to search,to look for,to sound out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"探る","answer":["さぐる"]},
    {"meaning":"to stick,to be stuck","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"刺さる","answer":["ささる"]},
    {"meaning":"hindrance,impediment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差し支え","answer":["さしつかえ"]},
    {"meaning":"deduction,subtraction,balance,ebb and flow,rise and fall","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差し引き","answer":["さしひき"]},
    {"meaning":"to pierce,to stab,to prick,to thrust","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"刺す","answer":["さす"]},
    {"meaning":"to pour (drink),to serve (drinks)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"注す","answer":["さす"]},
    {"meaning":"clever,adept,good,expectations,as one would expect","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流石","answer":["さすが"]},
    {"meaning":"at once,immediately,without delay,promptly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"早速","answer":["さっそく"]},
    {"meaning":"cushion (Japanese)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"座布団","answer":["ざぶとん"]},
    {"meaning":"to cool,to dampen,to let cool","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"冷ます","answer":["さます"]},
    {"meaning":"to become cool,to wear off,to abate,to subside","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"冷める","answer":["さめる"]},
    {"meaning":"month after next","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"再来月","answer":["さらいげつ"]},
    {"meaning":"week after next","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"再来週","answer":["さらいしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"year after next","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"再来年","answer":["さらいねん"]},
    {"meaning":"triangle,triangular","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"三角","answer":["さんかく"]},
    {"meaning":"arithmetic","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"算数","answer":["さんすう"]},
    {"meaning":"producing area","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"産地","answer":["さんち"]},
    {"meaning":"mountain forest,mountains and forest","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"山林","answer":["さんりん"]},
    {"meaning":"to be finished","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"仕上がる","answer":["しあがる"]},
    {"meaning":"temple","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"寺院","answer":["じいん"]},
    {"meaning":"salty (taste)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"塩辛い","answer":["しおからい"]},
    {"meaning":"square","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"四角","answer":["しかく"]},
    {"meaning":"square","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"四角い","answer":["しかくい"]},
    {"meaning":"timetable,schedule","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"時間割","answer":["じかんわり"]},
    {"meaning":"four seasons","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"四季","answer":["しき"]},
    {"meaning":"bringing,taking,carrying","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"持参","answer":["じさん"]},
    {"meaning":"rounding up (fractions)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"四捨五入","answer":["ししゃごにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"continuously,from beginning to end","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"始終","answer":["しじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"self-study","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"自習","answer":["じしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"natural science","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"自然科学","answer":["しぜんかがく"]},
    {"meaning":"speed (per hour)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"時速","answer":["じそく"]},
    {"meaning":"descendants,posterity,offspring","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"子孫","answer":["しそん"]},
    {"meaning":"corpse","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"死体","answer":["したい"]},
    {"meaning":"rough copy,draft","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"下書き","answer":["したがき"]},
    {"meaning":"Shitamachi,lower parts of town","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"下町","answer":["したまち"]},
    {"meaning":"self-government,autonomy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"自治","answer":["じち"]},
    {"meaning":"feelings (actual, true)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実感","answer":["じっかん"]},
    {"meaning":"moisture,humidity,dampness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"湿気","answer":["しっけ","しっき"]},
    {"meaning":"practice,training","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実習","answer":["じっしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"achievements,actual results","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"実績","answer":["じっせき"]},
    {"meaning":"level of humidity","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"湿度","answer":["しつど"]},
    {"meaning":"real thing,original","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実物","answer":["じつぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"practical use,utility","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実用","answer":["じつよう"]},
    {"meaning":"merit,efficiency,arms,force","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実力","answer":["じつりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"example,illustration","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実例","answer":["じつれい"]},
    {"meaning":"disappointed love,broken heart,unrequited love,be lovelorn","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"失恋","answer":["しつれん"]},
    {"meaning":"designation,specification,assignment,pointing at","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"指定","answer":["してい"]},
    {"meaning":"private railway","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"私鉄","answer":["してつ"]},
    {"meaning":"children,juvenile","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"児童","answer":["じどう"]},
    {"meaning":"plain,simple","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"地味","answer":["じみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be wet,to become wet,to be damp","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"湿る","answer":["しめる"]},
    {"meaning":"social science","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"社会科学","answer":["しゃかいかがく"]},
    {"meaning":"weak point,weakness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"弱点","answer":["じゃくてん"]},
    {"meaning":"garage,car shed","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"車庫","answer":["しゃこ"]},
    {"meaning":"sketching,drawing from nature","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"写生","answer":["しゃせい"]},
    {"meaning":"editorial,leading article","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"社説","answer":["しゃせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"(car) wheel","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"車輪","answer":["しゃりん"]},
    {"meaning":"meeting,assembly","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"集会","answer":["しゅうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"dwelling,house,residence,address","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"住居","answer":["じゅうきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"money collection","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"集金","answer":["しゅうきん"]},
    {"meaning":"gathering,assembly,meeting,set (math)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"集合","answer":["しゅうごう"]},
    {"meaning":"penmanship","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"習字","answer":["しゅうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"seriously ill,serious condition,critical state","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"重体","answer":["じゅうたい"]},
    {"meaning":"terminus,last stop (e.g train)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"終点","answer":["しゅうてん"]},
    {"meaning":"important point,lay stress on,colon,emphasis","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"重点","answer":["じゅうてん"]},
    {"meaning":"circumference,outskirts,environs,(computer) peripheral","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"周辺","answer":["しゅうへん"]},
    {"meaning":"director,high executive","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"重役","answer":["じゅうやく","おもやく"]},
    {"meaning":"end,close,termination","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"終了","answer":["しゅうりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) weight,(2) heavyweight boxer","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"重量","answer":["じゅうりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"gravity","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"重力","answer":["じゅうりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"national holiday","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"祝日","answer":["しゅくじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"taking an examination","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受験","answer":["じゅけん"]},
    {"meaning":"(gram) subject","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"主語","answer":["しゅご"]},
    {"meaning":"going to work,at work","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出勤","answer":["しゅっきん"]},
    {"meaning":"predicate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"述語","answer":["じゅつご"]},
    {"meaning":"leading part,leading actor (actress)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"主役","answer":["しゅやく"]},
    {"meaning":"pure heart,naivete,self-sacrificing devotion","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"純情","answer":["じゅんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"digestion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"消化","answer":["しょうか"]},
    {"meaning":"grade school student","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"小学生","answer":["しょうがくせい"]},
    {"meaning":"steam,vapour","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"蒸気","answer":["じょうき"]},
    {"meaning":"(measuring) ruler","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"定規","answer":["じょうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"commerce,trade,business","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"商業","answer":["しょうぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"prize,monetary award","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"賞金","answer":["しょうきん"]},
    {"meaning":"high and low,up and down,unloading and loading,praising and blaming","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"上下","answer":["じょうげ","うえした"]},
    {"meaning":"paper sliding door","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"障子","answer":["しょうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"trading company,firm","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"商社","answer":["しょうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"taking a train,entraining","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"乗車","answer":["じょうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"to cause,to arise,to be generated","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"生ずる","answer":["しょうずる"]},
    {"meaning":"fraction (part of),decimal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"小数","answer":["しょうすう"]},
    {"meaning":"shop,business firm","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"商店","answer":["しょうてん"]},
    {"meaning":"disinfection,sterilization","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"消毒","answer":["しょうどく"]},
    {"meaning":"victory or defeat,issue (of battle)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勝敗","answer":["しょうはい"]},
    {"meaning":"evaporation,unexplained disappearance","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"蒸発","answer":["じょうはつ"]},
    {"meaning":"prize,trophy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"賞品","answer":["しょうひん"]},
    {"meaning":"victory or defeat,match,contest,game,bout","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勝負","answer":["しょうぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"(col) urine,piss","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"小便","answer":["しょうべん"]},
    {"meaning":"fire station","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"消防署","answer":["しょうぼうしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"net (weight)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"正味","answer":["しょうみ"]},
    {"meaning":"the front,honesty","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"正面","answer":["しょうめん"]},
    {"meaning":"omission,abbreviation,abridgment","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"省略","answer":["しょうりゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"table salt","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"食塩","answer":["しょくえん"]},
    {"meaning":"worker,mechanic,artisan,craftsman","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"職人","answer":["しょくにん"]},
    {"meaning":"book,publication","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"書籍","answer":["しょせき"]},
    {"meaning":"bookshop","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"書店","answer":["しょてん"]},
    {"meaning":"calligraphy","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"書道","answer":["しょどう"]},
    {"meaning":"white or grey hair,trendy hair bleaching","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"白髪","answer":["しらが"]},
    {"meaning":"acquaintance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"知合い","answer":["しりあい"]},
    {"meaning":"private (establishment)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"私立","answer":["しりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"materials,data","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"資料","answer":["しりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"vacuum,hollow,empty","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真空","answer":["しんくう"]},
    {"meaning":"to believe,to believe in,to place trust in","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"信ずる","answer":["しんずる"]},
    {"meaning":"man-made,synthetic,artificial","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"人造","answer":["じんぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"bed,couch","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寝台","answer":["しんだい"]},
    {"meaning":"social sciences,humanities","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人文科学","answer":["じんぶんかがく"]},
    {"meaning":"(human) life","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人命","answer":["じんめい"]},
    {"meaning":"late at night","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"深夜","answer":["しんや"]},
    {"meaning":"forest,woods","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"森林","answer":["しんりん"]},
    {"meaning":"relation,kin","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"親類","answer":["しんるい"]},
    {"meaning":"course,direction,compass bearing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"針路","answer":["しんろ"]},
    {"meaning":"myth,legend","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"神話","answer":["しんわ"]},
    {"meaning":"marine products,fisheries","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"水産","answer":["すいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"water vapour,steam","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"水蒸気","answer":["すいじょうき"]},
    {"meaning":"drop of water","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"水滴","answer":["すいてき"]},
    {"meaning":"canteen,flask,water bottle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"水筒","answer":["すいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"essays,miscellaneous writings","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"随筆","answer":["ずいひつ"]},
    {"meaning":"water level,horizon","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"水平","answer":["すいへい"]},
    {"meaning":"horizon","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"水平線","answer":["すいへいせん"]},
    {"meaning":"Wednesday","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"水曜","answer":["すいよう"]},
    {"meaning":"youngest child","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"末っ子","answer":["すえっこ"]},
    {"meaning":"matter of taste","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"好き好き","answer":["すきずき"]},
    {"meaning":"crevice,crack,gap,opening","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"隙間","answer":["すきま"]},
    {"meaning":"figure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"図形","answer":["ずけい"]},
    {"meaning":"to cool oneself,to cool off,to enjoy evening cool","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"涼む","answer":["すずむ"]},
    {"meaning":"head,brains,intellect","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"頭脳","answer":["ずのう"]},
    {"meaning":"chart,diagram,graph","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"図表","answer":["ずひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"dwelling,house,residence,address","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"住まい","answer":["すまい"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"清む","answer":["すむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to print","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"刷る","answer":["する"]},
    {"meaning":"surname,family name","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"姓","answer":["せい"]},
    {"meaning":"customs house","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"税関","answer":["ぜいかん"]},
    {"meaning":"work (film, book)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"制作","answer":["せいさく"]},
    {"meaning":"nature,property,disposition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"性質","answer":["せいしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"clean copy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"清書","answer":["せいしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"youth,young person","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"青少年","answer":["せいしょうねん"]},
    {"meaning":"cleaning","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"清掃","answer":["せいそう"]},
    {"meaning":"existence,being,survival","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"生存","answer":["せいぞん"]},
    {"meaning":"growth,increment","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"生長","answer":["せいちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"(member of) political party","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"政党","answer":["せいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"birth date","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"生年月日","answer":["せいねんがっぴ"]},
    {"meaning":"ability,efficiency","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"性能","answer":["せいのう"]},
    {"meaning":"distinction by sex,sex,gender","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"性別","answer":["せいべつ"]},
    {"meaning":"square","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"正方形","answer":["せいほうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"main gate,main entrance","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"正門","answer":["せいもん"]},
    {"meaning":"coming into existence,arrangements,establishment,completion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"成立","answer":["せいりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be burdened with,to carry on back or shoulder","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"背負う","answer":["せおう","しょう"]},
    {"meaning":"equator","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"赤道","answer":["せきどう"]},
    {"meaning":"with trouble,at great pains,long-awaited","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"折角","answer":["せっかく"]},
    {"meaning":"getting closer,drawing nearer,approaching","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"接近","answer":["せっきん"]},
    {"meaning":"soap","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"石鹸","answer":["せっけん"]},
    {"meaning":"to come in contact with,to connect,to attend,to receive","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"接する","answer":["せっする"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) connection,union,join,link,(2) changing trains","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"接続","answer":["せつぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"around,throughout,front and back,before and behind,before and after","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"前後","answer":["ぜんご"]},
    {"meaning":"complete works","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全集","answer":["ぜんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"despotism,autocracy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"専制","answer":["せんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"month before last","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"先々月","answer":["せんせんげつ"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"先々週","answer":["せんせんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"ancestor","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"先祖","answer":["せんぞ"]},
    {"meaning":"head,lead,vanguard,first","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"先頭","answer":["せんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"(the) whole,universal,wholly,general","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"全般","answer":["ぜんぱん"]},
    {"meaning":"line,track,roadbed","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"線路","answer":["せんろ"]},
    {"meaning":"difference,discrepancy,variation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相違","answer":["そうい"]},
    {"meaning":"increase and decrease,fluctuation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"増減","answer":["ぞうげん"]},
    {"meaning":"mutual,reciprocal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相互","answer":["そうご"]},
    {"meaning":"shipbuilding","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"造船","answer":["ぞうせん"]},
    {"meaning":"enlargement","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"増大","answer":["ぞうだい"]},
    {"meaning":"farewell,send-off","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"送別","answer":["そうべつ"]},
    {"meaning":"Prime Minister","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"総理大臣","answer":["そうりだいじん"]},
    {"meaning":"postage,carriage","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"送料","answer":["そうりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"successively,one after another","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"続々","answer":["ぞくぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"express,special delivery","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"速達","answer":["そくたつ"]},
    {"meaning":"measurement","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"測定","answer":["そくてい"]},
    {"meaning":"measurement,surveying","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"測量","answer":["そくりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"speed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"速力","answer":["そくりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"ancestor","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"祖先","answer":["そせん"]},
    {"meaning":"frankness,candour,openheartedness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"卒直","answer":["そっちょく"]},
    {"meaning":"(hum) to know","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"存じる","answer":["ぞんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"存ずる","answer":["ぞんずる"]},
    {"meaning":"loss and gain,advantage and disadvantage","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"損得","answer":["そんとく"]},
    {"meaning":"paddy field,farm","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"田んぼ","answer":["たんぼ"]},
    {"meaning":"to leave hospital","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"退院","answer":["たいいん"]},
    {"meaning":"graduate school","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大学院","answer":["だいがくいん"]},
    {"meaning":"carpenter","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"大工","answer":["だいく"]},
    {"meaning":"drum,tambourine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"太鼓","answer":["たいこ"]},
    {"meaning":"(not so) much,(not) very","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大して","answer":["たいして"]},
    {"meaning":"contrast,antithesis,comparison","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"対照","answer":["たいしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"size","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大小","answer":["だいしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"order,system,structure,set-up,organization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"体制","answer":["たいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"capacity,volume","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"体積","answer":["たいせき"]},
    {"meaning":"very much,exaggerated,very fine","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"大層","answer":["たいそう"]},
    {"meaning":"large tree","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大木","answer":["たいぼく"]},
    {"meaning":"title","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"題名","answer":["だいめい"]},
    {"meaning":"pronoun","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"代名詞","answer":["だいめいし"]},
    {"meaning":"rice planting","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"田植え","answer":["たうえ"]},
    {"meaning":"constantly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"絶えず","answer":["たえず"]},
    {"meaning":"to till,to plow,to cultivate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"耕す","answer":["たがやす"]},
    {"meaning":"bamboo,middle (of a three-tier ranking system)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"竹","answer":["たけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be saved,to be rescued,to survive,to be helpful","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"助かる","answer":["たすかる"]},
    {"meaning":"to fold (clothes)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"畳む","answer":["たたむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to stop,to halt,to stand still","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"立ち止まる","answer":["たちどまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to erect,to be erected,to be built","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"建つ","answer":["たつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to depart (on a plane, train, etc.)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発つ","answer":["たつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to compare,to liken,to speak figuratively,to illustrate,to use a simile","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"例える","answer":["たとえる"]},
    {"meaning":"tabi,Japanese socks (with split toe)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"足袋","answer":["たび"]},
    {"meaning":"to be sufficient,to be enough","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"足る","answer":["たる"]},
    {"meaning":"gradation,grade,stage","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"段階","answer":["だんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"short term","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"短期","answer":["たんき"]},
    {"meaning":"coal mine,coal pit","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"炭鉱","answer":["たんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) defect,demerit,weak point,(2) disadvantage","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"短所","answer":["たんしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"water outage","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"断水","answer":["だんすい"]},
    {"meaning":"singular (number)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"単数","answer":["たんすう"]},
    {"meaning":"multi-unit apartments","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"団地","answer":["だんち"]},
    {"meaning":"conclusion,decision","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"断定","answer":["だんてい"]},
    {"meaning":"short (e.g. story, film)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"短編","answer":["たんぺん"]},
    {"meaning":"underground water","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"地下水","answer":["ちかすい"]},
    {"meaning":"nearness,before long","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"近々","answer":["ちかぢか","きんきん"]},
    {"meaning":"to bring near,to put close,to let come near,to associate with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"近付ける","answer":["ちかづける"]},
    {"meaning":"to approach,to draw near","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"近寄る","answer":["ちかよる"]},
    {"meaning":"reassuring,emboldened","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"力強い","answer":["ちからづよい"]},
    {"meaning":"geological features","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"地質","answer":["ちしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"friend,acquaintance","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"知人","answer":["ちじん"]},
    {"meaning":"area,zone","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"地帯","answer":["ちたい"]},
    {"meaning":"site,point on a map","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"地点","answer":["ちてん"]},
    {"meaning":"place name","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"地名","answer":["ちめい"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"茶色い","answer":["ちゃいろい"]},
    {"meaning":"steadily","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"着々","answer":["ちゃくちゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"middle,midway,interim","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"中間","answer":["ちゅうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"Middle Ages,mediaeval times","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"中世","answer":["ちゅうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"neuter gender,neutral (chem.),indifference,sterility","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"中性","answer":["ちゅうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"in the middle,half-way","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"中途","answer":["ちゅうと"]},
    {"meaning":"middle-aged","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"中年","answer":["ちゅうねん"]},
    {"meaning":"excess,being more than","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"超過","answer":["ちょうか"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) strong point,merit,(2) advantage","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"長所","answer":["ちょうしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"eldest daughter","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"長女","answer":["ちょうじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"length,long and short,+-","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"長短","answer":["ちょうたん"]},
    {"meaning":"top,summit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"頂点","answer":["ちょうてん"]},
    {"meaning":"eldest son","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"長男","answer":["ちょうなん"]},
    {"meaning":"rectangle,oblong","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"長方形","answer":["ちょうほうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"condiment,seasoning","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"調味料","answer":["ちょうみりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"immediately following","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直後","answer":["ちょくご"]},
    {"meaning":"straight line","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"直線","answer":["ちょくせん"]},
    {"meaning":"just before","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直前","answer":["ちょくぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"direct communication","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直通","answer":["ちょくつう"]},
    {"meaning":"direct current","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直流","answer":["ちょくりゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"storage,preservation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"貯蔵","answer":["ちょぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"right angle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"直角","answer":["ちょっかく"]},
    {"meaning":"to scatter around,to leave untidy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"散らかす","answer":["ちらかす"]},
    {"meaning":"to be in disorder,to lie scattered around","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"散らかる","answer":["ちらかる"]},
    {"meaning":"to scatter,to disperse,to distribute","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"散らす","answer":["ちらす"]},
    {"meaning":"to fall,to scatter (e.g. blossoms)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"散る","answer":["ちる"]},
    {"meaning":"addition,supplement,appendix","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"追加","answer":["ついか"]},
    {"meaning":"currency","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"通貨","answer":["つうか"]},
    {"meaning":"commuting to work","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"通勤","answer":["つうきん"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"通ずる","answer":["つうずる"]},
    {"meaning":"notice,notification","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"通知","answer":["つうち"]},
    {"meaning":"popular use,circulation","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"通用","answer":["つうよう"]},
    {"meaning":"passage,pathway","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"通路","answer":["つうろ"]},
    {"meaning":"to associate with,to keep company with,to get on with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"付合う","answer":["つきあう"]},
    {"meaning":"end (e.g. of street)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"突き当たり","answer":["つきあたり"]},
    {"meaning":"to run into,to collide with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"突き当たる","answer":["つきあたる"]},
    {"meaning":"time,years,days","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"月日","answer":["つきひ","がっぴ"]},
    {"meaning":"to catch fire,(electricity) comes on","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"点く","answer":["つく"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to thrust,to strike,(2) to poke","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"突く","answer":["つく","つつく"]},
    {"meaning":"to rank next to,to come after","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"次ぐ","answer":["つぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"to make","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"作る","answer":["つくる"]},
    {"meaning":"to make,to create","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"造る","answer":["つくる"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to attach,to join,to add,to append","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"着ける","answer":["つける"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn on,to switch on,to light up","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"点ける","answer":["つける"]},
    {"meaning":"to be handed down,to be introduced,to be transmitted","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"伝わる","answer":["つたわる"]},
    {"meaning":"to plunge into,to go into deeply","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"突っ込む","answer":["つっこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to serve,to fill a post,to serve under,to work (for)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"務める","answer":["つとめる"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to serve,to fill a post,to serve under,to work (for)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"努める","answer":["つとめる"]},
    {"meaning":"grain","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"粒","answer":["つぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be blocked,to be packed","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"詰まる","answer":["つまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to pile up,to stack","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"積む","answer":["つむ"]},
    {"meaning":"firm,strong","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"強気","answer":["つよき","ごうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"an encounter","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出合い","answer":["であい"]},
    {"meaning":"restroom,lavatory,hand-washing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手洗い","answer":["てあらい"]},
    {"meaning":"fixed number of regular personnel,capacity (of boat, etc.)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"定員","answer":["ていいん"]},
    {"meaning":"fall,decline,lowering,deterioration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"低下","answer":["ていか"]},
    {"meaning":"commuter pass,season ticket","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"定期券","answer":["ていきけん"]},
    {"meaning":"regular holiday","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"定休日","answer":["ていきゅうび"]},
    {"meaning":"suspension,interruption,stoppage,ban","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"停止","answer":["ていし"]},
    {"meaning":"stopping (e.g. train)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"停車","answer":["ていしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"failure of electricity","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"停電","answer":["ていでん"]},
    {"meaning":"in and out,coming and going,free association,income and expenditure,debits and credit","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"出入り","answer":["でいり"]},
    {"meaning":"exit and entrance","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出入口","answer":["でいりぐち"]},
    {"meaning":"repairs,maintenance","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"手入れ","answer":["ていれ"]},
    {"meaning":"to depart,to set out,to start,to be going out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出掛ける","answer":["でかける"]},
    {"meaning":"be finished,ready,made for,cut out","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"出来上がり","answer":["できあがり"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to be finished,to be ready,by definition,(2) to be very drunk","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"出来上がる","answer":["できあがる"]},
    {"meaning":"precise,accurate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"適確","answer":["てきかく"]},
    {"meaning":"wrist","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"手首","answer":["てくび"]},
    {"meaning":"moderate,handy","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"手頃","answer":["てごろ"]},
    {"meaning":"railway bridge,iron bridge","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"鉄橋","answer":["てっきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"procedure,(legal) process,formalities","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手続き","answer":["てつづき"]},
    {"meaning":"before,this side,we,you","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"手前","answer":["てまえ"]},
    {"meaning":"meeting,reception","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出迎え","answer":["でむかえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to meet,to greet","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出迎える","answer":["でむかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to shine on,to illuminate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"照らす","answer":["てらす"]},
    {"meaning":"to shine","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"照る","answer":["てる"]},
    {"meaning":"biography,life story","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"伝記","answer":["でんき"]},
    {"meaning":"light bulb","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"電球","answer":["でんきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"marks,points,score,runs","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"点数","answer":["てんすう"]},
    {"meaning":"battery","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"電池","answer":["でんち"]},
    {"meaning":"here and there,little by little","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"点々","answer":["てんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"転々","answer":["てんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"telephone pole,telegraph pole,lightpole","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"電柱","answer":["でんちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"electro-magnetic wave","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"電波","answer":["でんぱ"]},
    {"meaning":"electric current","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"電流","answer":["でんりゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"electric power","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"電力","answer":["でんりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"enquiry,ENQ","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"問い合わせ","answer":["といあわせ"]},
    {"meaning":"copper","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"銅","answer":["どう","あかがね"]},
    {"meaning":"the same rank,equality,apposition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"同格","answer":["どうかく"]},
    {"meaning":"action,movements,motions,bearing,behaviour,manners","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"動作","answer":["どうさ"]},
    {"meaning":"East and West,whole country","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"東西","answer":["とうざい"]},
    {"meaning":"appointed day,very day","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当日","answer":["とうじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"letter to the editor,letter from a reader,contribution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"投書","answer":["とうしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"entry (on stage)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"登場","answer":["とうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"lighthouse","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"灯台","answer":["とうだい"]},
    {"meaning":"theft,robbery","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"盗難","answer":["とうなん"]},
    {"meaning":"being on duty","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当番","answer":["とうばん"]},
    {"meaning":"lamp oil,kerosene","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"灯油","answer":["とうゆ"]},
    {"meaning":"Orient","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"東洋","answer":["とうよう"]},
    {"meaning":"fairy tale","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"童話","answer":["どうわ"]},
    {"meaning":"to happen to pass by","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"通り掛かる","answer":["とおりかかる"]},
    {"meaning":"to melt,to dissolve","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"溶かす","answer":["とかす"]},
    {"meaning":"to dissolve (paint)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"溶く","answer":["とく"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to retreat,to recede,to withdraw","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"退く","answer":["どく","しりぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"characteristic,feature","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"特色","answer":["とくしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"forte,merit","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"特長","answer":["とくちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"specific,special,particular","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"特定","answer":["とくてい"]},
    {"meaning":"special sale","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"特売","answer":["とくばい"]},
    {"meaning":"to melt into","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"溶け込む","answer":["とけこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to melt,to thaw,to fuse,to dissolve","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"溶ける","answer":["とける"]},
    {"meaning":"to remove,to take away,to dislodge,to put something out of the way","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"退ける","answer":["どける","しりぞける","のける"]},
    {"meaning":"alcove","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"床の間","answer":["とこのま"]},
    {"meaning":"barber","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"床屋","answer":["とこや"]},
    {"meaning":"here and there,some parts (of something)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"所々","answer":["ところどころ","しょしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"heart (of city)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"都心","answer":["としん"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to be fixed,(2) to abide,to stay (in the one place)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"留まる","answer":["とどまる","とまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to jump in,to leap in,to plunge into,to dive","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"飛び込む","answer":["とびこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to give shelter to,to lodge","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"泊める","answer":["とめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to seize,to grasp,to capture,to arrest","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"捕える","answer":["とらえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to harvest,to take in,to adopt","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り入れる","answer":["とりいれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to cancel","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り消す","answer":["とりけす"]},
    {"meaning":"to take out,to produce,to pick out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り出す","answer":["とりだす"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to adopt (measure, proposal),(2) to pick (fruit)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"採る","answer":["とる"]},
    {"meaning":"to take,to catch (fish),to capture","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"捕る","answer":["とる"]},
    {"meaning":"internist clinic,internal medicine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"内科","answer":["ないか"]},
    {"meaning":"phone extension,indoor wiring,inner line","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"内線","answer":["ないせん"]},
    {"meaning":"to cure,to heal,to fix,to correct,to repair","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"治す","answer":["なおす"]},
    {"meaning":"long,lengthy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"永い","answer":["ながい"]},
    {"meaning":"reconciliation,make peace with","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"仲直り","answer":["なかなおり"]},
    {"meaning":"to be prolonged,to drag on","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"長引く","answer":["ながびく"]},
    {"meaning":"contents,interior,substance,filling,(sword) blade","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"中味","answer":["なかみ"]},
    {"meaning":"middle finger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"中指","answer":["なかゆび","ちゅうし"]},
    {"meaning":"intimate friend,bosom buddy,chum","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"仲良し","answer":["なかよし"]},
    {"meaning":"to lose someone, wife, child, etc","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"亡くす","answer":["なくす"]},
    {"meaning":"impertinent,saucy,cheeky,conceit,audacious,brazen","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"生意気","answer":["なまいき"]},
    {"meaning":"roadside tree,row of trees","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"並木","answer":["なみき"]},
    {"meaning":"to bear fruit","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"生る","answer":["なる"]},
    {"meaning":"south pole,Antarctic","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"南極","answer":["なんきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"South America","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"南米","answer":["なんべい"]},
    {"meaning":"south and north","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"南北","answer":["なんぼく"]},
    {"meaning":"to let loose,to set free,to let escape","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"逃がす","answer":["にがす"]},
    {"meaning":"hateful,abominable,poor-looking,detestable","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"憎い","answer":["にくい"]},
    {"meaning":"to hate,to detest","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"憎む","answer":["にくむ"]},
    {"meaning":"odious,hateful","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"憎らしい","answer":["にくらしい"]},
    {"meaning":"date and time","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"日時","answer":["にちじ"]},
    {"meaning":"daily necessities","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"日用品","answer":["にちようひん"]},
    {"meaning":"daily lesson,daily work,daily routine","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"日課","answer":["にっか"]},
    {"meaning":"agenda","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"日程","answer":["にってい"]},
    {"meaning":"dull (e.g. a knife),thickheaded,slow (opposite of fast),stupid","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"鈍い","answer":["にぶい","のろい"]},
    {"meaning":"entry to a company","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"入社","answer":["にゅうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"to heat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"熱する","answer":["ねっする"]},
    {"meaning":"sleep-wear,nightclothes,pyjamas,nightgown,nightdress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寝間着","answer":["ねまき"]},
    {"meaning":"sleep-wear,nightclothes,pyjamas,nightgown,nightdress","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"寝巻","answer":["ねまき"]},
    {"meaning":"year,fiscal year,school year,term","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"年度","answer":["ねんど"]},
    {"meaning":"agricultural produce","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"農産物","answer":["のうさんぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"agricultural community,farm village,rural","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"農村","answer":["のうそん"]},
    {"meaning":"concentration,brightness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"濃度","answer":["のうど"]},
    {"meaning":"agricultural chemicals","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"農薬","answer":["のうやく"]},
    {"meaning":"all,entirely,completely,without exception","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"残らず","answer":["のこらず"]},
    {"meaning":"to lengthen,to stretch,to reach out,to grow (beard)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"延ばす","answer":["のばす"]},
    {"meaning":"to be prolonged","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"延びる","answer":["のびる"]},
    {"meaning":"up-train (going to Tokyo),ascent","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"上り","answer":["のぼり"]},
    {"meaning":"to rise","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"上る","answer":["あがる","のぼる"]},
    {"meaning":"(n) transfer (trains, buses, etc.)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乗り換え","answer":["のりかえ"]},
    {"meaning":"grey,gray,ashen","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"灰色","answer":["はいいろ"]},
    {"meaning":"(hum) (pol) seeing,look at","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"拝見","answer":["はいけん"]},
    {"meaning":"shop,stand","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"売店","answer":["ばいてん"]},
    {"meaning":"trade,buying and selling","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"売買","answer":["ばいばい"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to grow,to spring up,(2) to cut (teeth)","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"生える","answer":["はえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to measure,to weigh,to survey","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"量る","answer":["はかる"]},
    {"meaning":"to measure,to weigh,to survey","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"測る","answer":["はかる"]},
    {"meaning":"to sweep,to brush,to gather up","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"掃く","answer":["はく"]},
    {"meaning":"gear,cog-wheel","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"歯車","answer":["はぐるま"]},
    {"meaning":"to get between,to be caught in","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"挟まる","answer":["はさまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to interpose,to hold between,to insert","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"挟む","answer":["はさむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to begin with,first of all","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"始めに","answer":["はじめに"]},
    {"meaning":"to be disconnected,to get out of place,to be off,to be out (e.g. of gear)","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"外れる","answer":["はずれる"]},
    {"meaning":"underwear","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"肌着","answer":["はだぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"as was expected,really","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"果して","answer":["はたして"]},
    {"meaning":"expression (music),conceptualization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"発想","answer":["はっそう"]},
    {"meaning":"generation (e.g. power)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発電","answer":["はつでん"]},
    {"meaning":"sale","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発売","answer":["はつばい"]},
    {"meaning":"discussion,conference","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"話合い","answer":["はなしあい"]},
    {"meaning":"to accost a person,to talk (to someone)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"話し掛ける","answer":["はなしかける"]},
    {"meaning":"while talking,the line is busy","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"話中","answer":["はなしちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"fireworks","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"花火","answer":["はなび"]},
    {"meaning":"to leave,to get free,to cut oneself off","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"放れる","answer":["はなれる"]},
    {"meaning":"shuttlecock","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"羽根","answer":["はね"]},
    {"meaning":"fragment,splinter,broken piece","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"破片","answer":["はへん"]},
    {"meaning":"dentifrice,toothpaste","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"歯磨き","answer":["はみがき"]},
    {"meaning":"fast-talking","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"早口","answer":["はやくち"]},
    {"meaning":"to flourish,to thrive,to be popular,to come into fashion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流行る","answer":["はやる"]},
    {"meaning":"to deposit,to pay in","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"払い込む","answer":["はらいこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to repay,to pay back","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"払い戻す","answer":["はらいもどす"]},
    {"meaning":"wire","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"針金","answer":["はりがね"]},
    {"meaning":"reflection,influence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"反映","answer":["はんえい"]},
    {"meaning":"seal (used for signature)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"判子","answer":["はんこ"]},
    {"meaning":"hurrah, cheers","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"万歳","answer":["ばんざい"]},
    {"meaning":"judge,judiciary","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"判事","answer":["はんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"reflection,reconsideration,introspection,meditation,contemplation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"反省","answer":["はんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"house number,address","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"番地","answer":["ばんち"]},
    {"meaning":"peninsula","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"半島","answer":["はんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"exposure to the sun,sunny place","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"日当たり","answer":["ひあたり"]},
    {"meaning":"day trip","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"日帰り","answer":["ひがえり"]},
    {"meaning":"shadow","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"日陰","answer":["ひかげ"]},
    {"meaning":"to undertake,to take up,to take over","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引受る","answer":["ひきうける"]},
    {"meaning":"to repeat,to send back,to bring back","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引返す","answer":["ひきかえす"]},
    {"meaning":"subtraction","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"引算","answer":["ひきざん"]},
    {"meaning":"to pull out,to take out,to draw out,to withdraw","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引出す","answer":["ひきだす"]},
    {"meaning":"to detain,to check,to restrain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引き止める","answer":["ひきとめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be caught in,to be stuck in,to be cheated","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引っ掛かる","answer":["ひっかかる"]},
    {"meaning":"(taking) notes,copying","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"筆記","answer":["ひっき"]},
    {"meaning":"moving (dwelling etc.),changing residence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引越し","answer":["ひっこし"]},
    {"meaning":"to draw back,to sink,to cave in","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引っ込む","answer":["ひっこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"writer,author","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"筆者","answer":["ひっしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"necessities,necessary article,requisite,essential","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"必需品","answer":["ひつじゅひん"]},
    {"meaning":"index finger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人差指","answer":["ひとさしゆび"]},
    {"meaning":"ordinary,usual,in general,briefly","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一通り","answer":["ひととおり"]},
    {"meaning":"pedestrian traffic","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"人通り","answer":["ひとどおり"]},
    {"meaning":"a rest","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"一休み","answer":["ひとやすみ"]},
    {"meaning":"cynicism,sarcasm","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"皮肉","answer":["ひにく"]},
    {"meaning":"every day,daily,day after day","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"日日","answer":["ひにち"]},
    {"meaning":"sunset","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"日の入り","answer":["ひのいり"]},
    {"meaning":"sunrise","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"日の出","answer":["ひので"]},
    {"meaning":"skin","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"皮膚","answer":["ひふ"]},
    {"meaning":"to cool,to refrigerate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"冷やす","answer":["ひやす"]},
    {"meaning":"beauty of figure or form","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"美容","answer":["びよう"]},
    {"meaning":"front cover,binding","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"表紙","answer":["ひょうし"]},
    {"meaning":"nap (at home),siesta","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"昼寝","answer":["ひるね"]},
    {"meaning":"to spread,to extend,to expand,to enlarge","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"広げる","answer":["ひろげる"]},
    {"meaning":"extent","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"広さ","answer":["ひろさ"]},
    {"meaning":"plaza","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"広場","answer":["ひろば"]},
    {"meaning":"extensive,spacious","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"広々","answer":["ひろびろ"]},
    {"meaning":"to broaden,to propagate","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"広める","answer":["ひろめる"]},
    {"meaning":"bottling,bottled","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"瓶詰","answer":["びんづめ"]},
    {"meaning":"balloon","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"風船","answer":["ふうせん"]},
    {"meaning":"unlucky,misfortune,bad luck,fate","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不運","answer":["ふうん"]},
    {"meaning":"to deepen,to heighten,to intensify","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"深まる","answer":["ふかまる"]},
    {"meaning":"irregularity,unsteadiness,disorderly","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"不規則","answer":["ふきそく"]},
    {"meaning":"neighbourhood,vicinity,environs","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"付近","answer":["ふきん"]},
    {"meaning":"adverb","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"副詞","answer":["ふくし"]},
    {"meaning":"copy,duplicate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"複写","answer":["ふくしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"plural,multiple","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"複数","answer":["ふくすう"]},
    {"meaning":"to include,to instruct,to make one understand","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"含める","answer":["ふくめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to get late,to advance,to wear on","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"更ける","answer":["ふける"]},
    {"meaning":"sign,mark,symbol","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"符号","answer":["ふごう"]},
    {"meaning":"man and wife,married couple","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"夫妻","answer":["ふさい"]},
    {"meaning":"radical (of a kanji character)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"部首","answer":["ぶしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"suspension,interruption,stoppage,tie-up,cessation","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不通","answer":["ふつう"]},
    {"meaning":"dangerous,disturbed,insecure","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"物騒","answer":["ぶっそう"]},
    {"meaning":"surface mail (ship)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"船便","answer":["ふなびん"]},
    {"meaning":"parts,accessories","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"部品","answer":["ぶひん"]},
    {"meaning":"snow storm","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"吹雪","answer":["ふぶき"]},
    {"meaning":"father and mother,parents","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"父母","answer":["ふぼ","ちちはは"]},
    {"meaning":"to increase,to add to,to augment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"増やす","answer":["ふやす"]},
    {"meaning":"literature,art and literature,belles-lettres","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"文芸","answer":["ぶんげい"]},
    {"meaning":"literary style","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"文体","answer":["ぶんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"closure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"閉会","answer":["へいかい"]},
    {"meaning":"coolness,calmness,composure,unconcern","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平気","answer":["へいき"]},
    {"meaning":"(going) side by side,concurrent,abreast,at the same time","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"並行","answer":["へいこう"]},
    {"meaning":"weekday,ordinary days","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平日","answer":["へいじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"soldier,sailor","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"兵隊","answer":["へいたい"]},
    {"meaning":"plain,open field","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平野","answer":["へいや"]},
    {"meaning":"separately,individually","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"別々","answer":["べつべつ"]},
    {"meaning":"editing,compilation,editorial (e.g. committee)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"編集","answer":["へんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"toilet,lavatory,rest room,latrine,comfort station","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"便所","answer":["べんじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"direction,way,compass point","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"方角","answer":["ほうがく"]},
    {"meaning":"dialect","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"方言","answer":["ほうげん"]},
    {"meaning":"prevention,check","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"防止","answer":["ぼうし"]},
    {"meaning":"objective,plan,policy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"方針","answer":["ほうしん"]},
    {"meaning":"packing,wrapping","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"包装","answer":["ほうそう"]},
    {"meaning":"law,rule","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"法則","answer":["ほうそく"]},
    {"meaning":"bandage,dressing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"包帯","answer":["ほうたい"]},
    {"meaning":"equation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"方程式","answer":["ほうていしき"]},
    {"meaning":"prevention of crime","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"防犯","answer":["ぼうはん"]},
    {"meaning":"direction,district,field (e.g., of study)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"方面","answer":["ほうめん"]},
    {"meaning":"to let go","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"放る","answer":["ほうる"]},
    {"meaning":"recruiting,taking applications","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"募集","answer":["ぼしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to air,to dry,to desiccate,to drain (off),to drink up","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"干す","answer":["ほす"]},
    {"meaning":"North Pole","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"北極","answer":["ほっきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"to dig,to excavate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"掘る","answer":["ほる"]},
    {"meaning":"headquarters","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"本部","answer":["ほんぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"essentially,naturally,by nature","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"本来","answer":["ほんらい"]},
    {"meaning":"the number of flat things","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"枚数","answer":["まいすう"]},
    {"meaning":"each time,common service-sector greeting","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"毎度","answer":["まいど"]},
    {"meaning":"to wind,to coil,to roll","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"巻く","answer":["まく"]},
    {"meaning":"to bend,to crook,to lean","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"曲げる","answer":["まげる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be mixed,to be blended with,to associate with,to mingle with,to join","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"混ざる","answer":["まざる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be mixed,to be blended with,to associate with,to mingle with,to join","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交ざる","answer":["まざる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be mixed,to be blended with,to associate with","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"混じる","answer":["まじる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be mixed,to be blended with,to associate with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交じる","answer":["まじる"]},
    {"meaning":"to mix,to stir","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"混ぜる","answer":["まぜる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be mixed,to be blended with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交ぜる","answer":["まぜる"]},
    {"meaning":"waiting room","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"待合室","answer":["まちあいしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to rendezvous,to meet at a prearranged place and time","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"待ち合わせる","answer":["まちあわせる"]},
    {"meaning":"total darkness,shortsightedness,pitch dark","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"真っ暗","answer":["まっくら"]},
    {"meaning":"pitch black","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真っ黒","answer":["まっくろ"]},
    {"meaning":"deep blue,ghastly pale","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真っ青","answer":["まっさお"]},
    {"meaning":"the head,the foremost,beginning","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真っ先","answer":["まっさき"]},
    {"meaning":"pure white","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真っ白","answer":["まっしろ"]},
    {"meaning":"to deify,to enshrine","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"祭る","answer":["まつる"]},
    {"meaning":"ticket window","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"窓口","answer":["まどぐち"]},
    {"meaning":"to mimic,to imitate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"真似る","answer":["まねる"]},
    {"meaning":"round,circular","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"円い","answer":["まるい"]},
    {"meaning":"detour","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回り道","answer":["まわりみち"]},
    {"meaning":"full house,no vacancy,sold out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"満員","answer":["まんいん"]},
    {"meaning":"perfect score","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"満点","answer":["まんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to see off,to farewell,(2) to escort,(3) to let pass","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"見送る","answer":["みおくる"]},
    {"meaning":"to overlook,to command a view of,to look down on something","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"見下ろす","answer":["みおろす"]},
    {"meaning":"outward appearance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見掛け","answer":["みかけ"]},
    {"meaning":"new moon,crescent moon","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"三日月","answer":["みかづき","みかずき"]},
    {"meaning":"store,shop","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"店屋","answer":["みせや"]},
    {"meaning":"heading,caption,subtitle,index","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"見出し","answer":["みだし"]},
    {"meaning":"itinerary,route","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"道順","answer":["みちじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"to be found,to be discovered","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見付かる","answer":["みつかる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be familiar,to discover,to detect","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見付ける","answer":["みつける"]},
    {"meaning":"to look again,to get a better opinion of","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見直す","answer":["みなおす"]},
    {"meaning":"to become used to seeing,to be familiar with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見慣れる","answer":["みなれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to bear fruit,to ripen","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実る","answer":["みのる"]},
    {"meaning":"sample","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"見本","answer":["みほん"]},
    {"meaning":"to ask after (health),to visit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見舞う","answer":["みまう"]},
    {"meaning":"less than,insufficient","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"未満","answer":["みまん"]},
    {"meaning":"surname,family name","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"名字","answer":["みょうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"private,civilian,civil,popular,folk,unofficial","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"民間","answer":["みんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"(v5u) to face,to go towards","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"向う","answer":["むかう"]},
    {"meaning":"to steam,to poultice,to be sultry","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"蒸す","answer":["むす"]},
    {"meaning":"group,crowd,flock,herd","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"群れ","answer":["むれ"]},
    {"meaning":"masterpiece","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"名作","answer":["めいさく"]},
    {"meaning":"business card","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"名刺","answer":["めいし"]},
    {"meaning":"noun","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"名詞","answer":["めいし"]},
    {"meaning":"famous place","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"名所","answer":["めいしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"to command,to appoint","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"命ずる","answer":["めいずる"]},
    {"meaning":"superstition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"迷信","answer":["めいしん"]},
    {"meaning":"famous product,special product,speciality","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"名物","answer":["めいぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"superior(s),senior","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"目上","answer":["めうえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to aim at,to have an eye on","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"目指す","answer":["めざす"]},
    {"meaning":"(abbr) alarm-clock","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"目覚まし","answer":["めざまし"]},
    {"meaning":"at present,now","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"目下","answer":["めした"]},
    {"meaning":"mark,sign,landmark","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"目印","answer":["めじるし"]},
    {"meaning":"to be conspicuous,to stand out","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"目立つ","answer":["めだつ"]},
    {"meaning":"criterion,aim","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"目安","answer":["めやす"]},
    {"meaning":"area","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"面積","answer":["めんせき"]},
    {"meaning":"interview","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"面接","answer":["めんせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"lumber,timber,wood","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"木材","answer":["もくざい"]},
    {"meaning":"table of contents","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"目次","answer":["もくじ"]},
    {"meaning":"originally,by nature,from the start","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"元々","answer":["もともと"]},
    {"meaning":"storage room","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"物置","answer":["ものおき"]},
    {"meaning":"to tell,to indicate","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"物語る","answer":["ものがたる"]},
    {"meaning":"ruler,measure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"物差し","answer":["ものさし"]},
    {"meaning":"to burn","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"燃やす","answer":["もやす"]},
    {"meaning":"questions and answers,dialogue","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"問答","answer":["もんどう"]},
    {"meaning":"at night,nighttime","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"夜間","answer":["やかん"]},
    {"meaning":"actor,actress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役者","answer":["やくしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"government office,public office","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役所","answer":["やくしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"government official","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役人","answer":["やくにん"]},
    {"meaning":"medicine(s),chemical(s)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"薬品","answer":["やくひん"]},
    {"meaning":"duty,business","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役目","answer":["やくめ"]},
    {"meaning":"walking around at night,night train,night travel","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"夜行","answer":["やこう","やぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"pharmacy,drugstore","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"薬局","answer":["やっきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"landlord","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"家主","answer":["やぬし","いえぬし"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"破く","answer":["やぶく"]},
    {"meaning":"to get torn,to wear out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"破れる","answer":["やぶれる"]},
    {"meaning":"soft,tender,limp","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"軟らかい","answer":["やわらかい"]},
    {"meaning":"amusement park","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遊園地","answer":["ゆうえんち"]},
    {"meaning":"evening paper","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"夕刊","answer":["ゆうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"friendship","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"友好","answer":["ゆうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"mailing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"郵送","answer":["ゆうそう"]},
    {"meaning":"(sudden) evening shower (rain)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"夕立","answer":["ゆうだち"]},
    {"meaning":"(in) the evening sun,setting sun","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"夕日","answer":["ゆうひ"]},
    {"meaning":"admission-paid,toll","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"有料","answer":["ゆうりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"bathrobe,informal summer kimono,yukata","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"浴衣","answer":["ゆかた"]},
    {"meaning":"steam,vapour","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"湯気","answer":["ゆげ"]},
    {"meaning":"blood transfusion","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"輸血","answer":["ゆけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"transport,transportation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"輸送","answer":["ゆそう"]},
    {"meaning":"negligence,unpreparedness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"油断","answer":["ゆだん"]},
    {"meaning":"teacup","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"湯飲み","answer":["ゆのみ"]},
    {"meaning":"lava","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"溶岩","answer":["ようがん"]},
    {"meaning":"term,terminology","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"用語","answer":["ようご"]},
    {"meaning":"infant,baby,child","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"幼児","answer":["ようじ"]},
    {"meaning":"capacity,volume","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"容積","answer":["ようせき"]},
    {"meaning":"use,usefulness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"用途","answer":["ようと"]},
    {"meaning":"shop which handles Western-style apparel and accessories","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"洋品店","answer":["ようひんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"point,gist,essentials,outline","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"要領","answer":["ようりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"too much,unnecessary,abundance,surplus,excess,superfluity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"余計","answer":["よけい"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to disgrace,to dishonour,(2) to pollute,to contaminate,to soil,to make dirty,to stain","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"汚す","answer":["よごす","けがす"]},
    {"meaning":"to collect,to gather,to add,to put aside","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寄せる","answer":["よせる"]},
    {"meaning":"four corners,crossroads","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"四つ角","answer":["よつかど"]},
    {"meaning":"preparation,preliminaries,reserve,spare","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予備","answer":["よび"]},
    {"meaning":"to call out to,to accost,to address (crowd),to appeal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"呼び掛ける","answer":["よびかける"]},
    {"meaning":"to summon,to call (e.g. phone)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"呼び出す","answer":["よびだす"]},
    {"meaning":"arrival in Japan,coming to Japan,visit to Japan","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"来日","answer":["らいにち"]},
    {"meaning":"rude,violent,rough,lawless,unreasonable,reckless","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乱暴","answer":["らんぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"science","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"理科","answer":["りか"]},
    {"meaning":"advantages and disadvantages,interest","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"利害","answer":["りがい"]},
    {"meaning":"to abbreviate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"略す","answer":["りゃくす"]},
    {"meaning":"(river) basin","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"流域","answer":["りゅういき"]},
    {"meaning":"both sides","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"両側","answer":["りょうがわ"]},
    {"meaning":"fisherman","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"漁師","answer":["りょうし"]},
    {"meaning":"consul","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"領事","answer":["りょうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"receipt,voucher","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"領収","answer":["りょうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"care-taking,caretaker,house-watching","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"留守番","answer":["るすばん"]},
    {"meaning":"exception","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"例外","answer":["れいがい"]},
    {"meaning":"zero,no marks","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"零点","answer":["れいてん"]},
    {"meaning":"freezing,cold storage,refrigeration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"冷凍","answer":["れいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"chain of islands","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"列島","answer":["れっとう"]},
    {"meaning":"union,alliance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"連合","answer":["れんごう"]},
    {"meaning":"(audio) recording","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"録音","answer":["ろくおん"]},
    {"meaning":"to argue,to discuss,to debate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"論ずる","answer":["ろんずる"]},
    {"meaning":"Japanese-English","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"和英","answer":["わえい"]},
    {"meaning":"youthful,young","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"若々しい","answer":["わかわかしい"]},
    {"meaning":"Japanese clothes","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"和服","answer":["わふく"]},
    {"meaning":"division (math)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"割算","answer":["わりざん"]},
    {"meaning":"relatively, comparitively","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"割と","answer":["わりと"]},
    {"meaning":"discount,reduction,rebate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"割引","answer":["わりびき"]},
    {"meaning":"sweat,perspiration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"汗","answer":["あせ"]},
    {"meaning":"vicinity,nearby","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"辺り","answer":["あたり","ほとり"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) trace,tracks,mark,sign,(2) remains,ruins,(3) scar","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"跡","answer":["あと"]},
    {"meaning":"to bathe,to bask in the sun,to shower","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"浴びる","answer":["あびる"]},
    {"meaning":"oil","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"油","answer":["あぶら"]},
    {"meaning":"stomach","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"胃","answer":["い"]},
    {"meaning":"committee member","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"委員","answer":["いいん"]},
    {"meaning":"force,vigor,energy,spirit","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"勢い","answer":["いきおい"]},
    {"meaning":"spring,fountain","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"泉","answer":["いずみ"]},
    {"meaning":"board,plank","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"板","answer":["いた"]},
    {"meaning":"much more,still more,all the more","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"一層","answer":["いっそう"]},
    {"meaning":"general,liberal,universal,ordinary,average","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"一般","answer":["いっぱん"]},
    {"meaning":"removal,migration,movement","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"移動","answer":["いどう"]},
    {"meaning":"clothes","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"衣服","answer":["いふく"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) request,commission,dispatch,(2) dependence,trust","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"依頼","answer":["いらい"]},
    {"meaning":"medical care,medical treatment","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"医療","answer":["いりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"rock,crag","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"岩","answer":["いわ"]},
    {"meaning":"celebration,festival","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"祝い","answer":["いわい"]},
    {"meaning":"to congratulate,to celebrate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"祝う","answer":["いわう"]},
    {"meaning":"printing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"印刷","answer":["いんさつ"]},
    {"meaning":"impression","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"印象","answer":["いんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"(hon) to visit,to ask,to inquire","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"伺う","answer":["うかがう"]},
    {"meaning":"to remove,to transfer,to infect","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"移す","answer":["うつす"]},
    {"meaning":"to betray,to turn traitor to,to double-cross","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"裏切る","answer":["うらぎる"]},
    {"meaning":"eternity,perpetuity,immortality,permanence","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"永遠","answer":["えいえん"]},
    {"meaning":"eternity,perpetuity,immortality","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"永久","answer":["えいきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"business,trade,management","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"営業","answer":["えいぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"nutrition,nourishment","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"栄養","answer":["えいよう"]},
    {"meaning":"postponement,adjournment","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"延期","answer":["えんき"]},
    {"meaning":"acting,performance","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"演技","answer":["えんぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"interior,inner part","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"奥","answer":["おく"]},
    {"meaning":"to send,to give to,to award to,to confer on","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"贈る","answer":["おくる"]},
    {"meaning":"very young,childish","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"幼い","answer":["おさない"]},
    {"meaning":"band (e.g. conduction, valence)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"帯","answer":["おび"]},
    {"meaning":"temperature","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"温度","answer":["おんど"]},
    {"meaning":"counter for chapters (of a book)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"課","answer":["か"]},
    {"meaning":"pleasant,agreeable,comfortable","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"快適","answer":["かいてき"]},
    {"meaning":"recovery (from illness),improvement,rehabilitation,restoration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"回復","answer":["かいふく"]},
    {"meaning":"to exchange,to interchange,to substitute,to replace","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"替える","answer":["かえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to exchange,to interchange,to substitute,to replace","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"換える","answer":["かえる"]},
    {"meaning":"addition and subtraction,allowance for","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"加減","answer":["かげん"]},
    {"meaning":"to surround,to encircle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"囲む","answer":["かこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"pastry","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"菓子","answer":["かし"]},
    {"meaning":"wise,clever,smart","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"賢い","answer":["かしこい"]},
    {"meaning":"mold,model,style,shape,data-type","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"型","answer":["かた"]},
    {"meaning":"shoulder","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"肩","answer":["かた"]},
    {"meaning":"solid,hard (esp. metal, stone),unpolished writing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"硬い","answer":["かたい"]},
    {"meaning":"to suffer","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"被る","answer":["かぶる"]},
    {"meaning":"hair (head)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"髪の毛","answer":["かみのけ"]},
    {"meaning":"river,stream","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"河","answer":["かわ"]},
    {"meaning":"skin,hide,leather,fur,pelt,bark,shell","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"皮","answer":["かわ"]},
    {"meaning":"can,tin","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"缶","answer":["かん"]},
    {"meaning":"a patient","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"患者","answer":["かんじゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"control,management (e.g. of a business)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"管理","answer":["かんり"]},
    {"meaning":"completion,conclusion","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"完了","answer":["かんりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"temperature","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"気温","answer":["きおん"]},
    {"meaning":"machine,mechanism","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"機械","answer":["きかい"]},
    {"meaning":"to be effective","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"効く","answer":["きく"]},
    {"meaning":"bank,coast,shore","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"岸","answer":["きし"]},
    {"meaning":"engineer,technician","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"技師","answer":["ぎし"]},
    {"meaning":"pitiful,a pity","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"気の毒","answer":["きのどく"]},
    {"meaning":"hope,wish,aspiration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"希望","answer":["きぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"reverse,opposite","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"逆","answer":["ぎゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"ex-","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"旧","answer":["きゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"game,match,contest","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"競技","answer":["きょうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"cooperation,collaboration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"協力","answer":["きょうりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"huge,gigantic,enormous","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"巨大","answer":["きょだい"]},
    {"meaning":"record,minutes,document","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"記録","answer":["きろく"]},
    {"meaning":"No Smoking!","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"禁煙","answer":["きんえん"]},
    {"meaning":"safe,vault,treasury,provider of funds","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"金庫","answer":["きんこ","かねぐら"]},
    {"meaning":"prohibition,ban","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"禁止","answer":["きんし"]},
    {"meaning":"pipe,tube","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"管","answer":["くだ","かん"]},
    {"meaning":"distinction,differentiation,classification","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"区別","answer":["くべつ"]},
    {"meaning":"cloudiness,cloudy weather,shadow","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"曇","answer":["くもり"]},
    {"meaning":"native Japanese reading of a Chinese character","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"訓","answer":["くん"]},
    {"meaning":"army,force,troops","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"軍","answer":["ぐん","いくさ"]},
    {"meaning":"army,troops","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"軍隊","answer":["ぐんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"practice,training","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"訓練","answer":["くんれん"]},
    {"meaning":"respect,honour","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"敬意","answer":["けいい"]},
    {"meaning":"management,administration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"経営","answer":["けいえい"]},
    {"meaning":"tendency,trend,inclination","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"傾向","answer":["けいこう"]},
    {"meaning":"calculation,reckoning","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"計算","answer":["けいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"(fine) art,the arts","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"芸術","answer":["げいじゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"drama,play","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"劇","answer":["げき"]},
    {"meaning":"theatre,playhouse","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"劇場","answer":["げきじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"ticket,coupon,bond,certificate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"券","answer":["けん"]},
    {"meaning":"prefecture","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"県","answer":["けん"]},
    {"meaning":"eaves","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"軒","answer":["けん","のき"]},
    {"meaning":"phenomenon","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"現象","answer":["げんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"construction,establishment","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"建設","answer":["けんせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"construction,architecture","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"建築","answer":["けんちく"]},
    {"meaning":"love,tender passion","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"恋","answer":["こい"]},
    {"meaning":"thick (as of color, liquid),dense,strong","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"濃い","answer":["こい"]},
    {"meaning":"lover,sweetheart","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"恋人","answer":["こいびと"]},
    {"meaning":"lecture,address","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"講演","answer":["こうえん"]},
    {"meaning":"effect,effectiveness,efficacy,result","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"効果","answer":["こうか"]},
    {"meaning":"coin","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"硬貨","answer":["こうか"]},
    {"meaning":"exchange,interchange,reciprocity","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"交換","answer":["こうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"aviation,flying","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"航空","answer":["こうくう"]},
    {"meaning":"candidacy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"候補","answer":["こうほ"]},
    {"meaning":"ice,hail","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"氷","answer":["こおり"]},
    {"meaning":"to freeze,to be frozen over,to congeal","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"凍る","answer":["こおる"]},
    {"meaning":"quite,very","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"極","answer":["ごく"]},
    {"meaning":"blackboard","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"黒板","answer":["こくばん"]},
    {"meaning":"hip","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"腰","answer":["こし"]},
    {"meaning":"individual,private person,personal,private","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"個人","answer":["こじん"]},
    {"meaning":"national or state border","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"国境","answer":["こっきょう","くにざかい"]},
    {"meaning":"parcel,package","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"小包","answer":["こづつみ"]},
    {"meaning":"flour,meal,powder","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"粉","answer":["こな"]},
    {"meaning":"confusion,congestion","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"混雑","answer":["こんざつ"]},
    {"meaning":"disorder,chaos,confusion,mayhem","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"混乱","answer":["こんらん"]},
    {"meaning":"least,lowest,worst","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"最低","answer":["さいてい"]},
    {"meaning":"ingredients,material","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"材料","answer":["ざいりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"border,boundary,mental state","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"境","answer":["さかい"]},
    {"meaning":"to go against,to oppose,to disobey,to defy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"逆らう","answer":["さからう"]},
    {"meaning":"to shout,to cry","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"叫ぶ","answer":["さけぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) token,label,(2) ticket,(3) charm","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"札","answer":["さつ"]},
    {"meaning":"plate,dish","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"皿","answer":["さら"]},
    {"meaning":"to sink,to feel depressed","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"沈む","answer":["しずむ"]},
    {"meaning":"leadership,guidance,coaching","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"指導","answer":["しどう"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to comprise,to account for,to make up (of),(2) to hold,to occupy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"占める","answer":["しめる"]},
    {"meaning":"sandbank","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"州","answer":["しゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"surroundings,circumference,environs","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"周囲","answer":["しゅうい"]},
    {"meaning":"group,mass","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"集団","answer":["しゅうだん"]},
    {"meaning":"lodging","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"宿泊","answer":["しゅくはく"]},
    {"meaning":"publication","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"出版","answer":["しゅっぱん"]},
    {"meaning":"preparation,arrangements,provision,reserve","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"準備","answer":["じゅんび"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) chapter,section,(2) medal","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"章","answer":["しょう"]},
    {"meaning":"prize,award","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"賞","answer":["しょう"]},
    {"meaning":"state of affairs,situation,circumstances","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"状況","answer":["じょうきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"consent,acceptance,assent,admitting","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"承知","answer":["しょうち"]},
    {"meaning":"recognition,acknowledgement,approval,consent,agreement","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"承認","answer":["しょうにん"]},
    {"meaning":"plant,vegetation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"植物","answer":["しょくぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"signature","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"署名","answer":["しょめい"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) mark,(2) symbol,(3) evidence","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"印","answer":["しるし","いん"]},
    {"meaning":"castle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"城","answer":["しろ"]},
    {"meaning":"heart","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"心臓","answer":["しんぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) water level,(2) level,standard","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"水準","answer":["すいじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"horn","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"角","answer":["すみ","かど","かく"]},
    {"meaning":"pointed,sharp","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"鋭い","answer":["するどい"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"税","answer":["ぜい"]},
    {"meaning":"tax,duty","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"税金","answer":["ぜいきん"]},
    {"meaning":"results,record","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"成績","answer":["せいせき"]},
    {"meaning":"government,administration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"政府","answer":["せいふ"]},
    {"meaning":"coal","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"石炭","answer":["せきたん"]},
    {"meaning":"oil,petroleum,kerosene","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"石油","answer":["せきゆ"]},
    {"meaning":"plan,design","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"設計","answer":["せっけい"]},
    {"meaning":"equipment,device,facilities,installation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"設備","answer":["せつび"]},
    {"meaning":"elephant","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"象","answer":["ぞう","しょう"]},
    {"meaning":"cleaning,sweeping","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"掃除","answer":["そうじ","そうじする"]},
    {"meaning":"imagination,guess","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"想像","answer":["そうぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"equipment,installation,apparatus","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"装置","answer":["そうち"]},
    {"meaning":"bottom,sole","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"底","answer":["そこ"]},
    {"meaning":"loss,disadvantage","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"損","answer":["そん"]},
    {"meaning":"damage,injury,loss","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"損害","answer":["そんがい"]},
    {"meaning":"respect,esteem,reverence,honour","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"尊敬","answer":["そんけい"]},
    {"meaning":"respect,esteem,regard","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"尊重","answer":["そんちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"temperature (body)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"体温","answer":["たいおん"]},
    {"meaning":"target,object (of worship, study, etc),subject (of taxation, etc)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"対象","answer":["たいしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"cabinet minister","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"大臣","answer":["だいじん"]},
    {"meaning":"treasure","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"宝","answer":["たから"]},
    {"meaning":"valley","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"谷","answer":["たに"]},
    {"meaning":"ball,sphere,coin","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"玉","answer":["たま","ぎょく"]},
    {"meaning":"simplicity","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"単純","answer":["たんじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"organization,association","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"団体","answer":["だんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"(in) charge","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"担当","answer":["たんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"area,region","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"地域","answer":["ちいき"]},
    {"meaning":"district,section,sector","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"地区","answer":["ちく"]},
    {"meaning":"horizon","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"地平線","answer":["ちへいせん"]},
    {"meaning":"centre,central,center,middle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"中央","answer":["ちゅうおう"]},
    {"meaning":"investigation,examination,inquiry,survey","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"調査","answer":["ちょうさ"]},
    {"meaning":"(bank) savings","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"貯金","answer":["ちょきん"]},
    {"meaning":"direct,immediate,personal,firsthand","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"直接","answer":["ちょくせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"author,writer","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"著者","answer":["ちょしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"bundle,package,parcel,bale","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"包み","answer":["つつみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to pack,to shorten,to work out (details)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"詰める","answer":["つめる"]},
    {"meaning":"painful,heart-breaking","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"辛い","answer":["つらい","からい"]},
    {"meaning":"bus or tram stop","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"停留所","answer":["ていりゅうじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"iron","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"鉄","answer":["てつ"]},
    {"meaning":"railroad","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"鉄道","answer":["てつどう"]},
    {"meaning":"party (political)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"党","answer":["とう"]},
    {"meaning":"tower,pagoda","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"塔","answer":["とう"]},
    {"meaning":"verb","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"動詞","answer":["どうし"]},
    {"meaning":"poison,toxicant","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"毒","answer":["どく"]},
    {"meaning":"to reach","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"届く","answer":["とどく"]},
    {"meaning":"mud","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"泥","answer":["どろ"]},
    {"meaning":"relation,relationship","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"仲","answer":["なか"]},
    {"meaning":"company,fellow,colleague,associate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"仲間","answer":["なかま"]},
    {"meaning":"wave","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"波","answer":["なみ"]},
    {"meaning":"tear","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"涙","answer":["なみだ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be worried,to be troubled","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"悩む","answer":["なやむ"]},
    {"meaning":"cloth","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"布","answer":["ぬの"]},
    {"meaning":"root","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"根","answer":["ね"]},
    {"meaning":"tropics","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"熱帯","answer":["ねったい"]},
    {"meaning":"farmer,farm family","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"農家","answer":["のうか"]},
    {"meaning":"agriculture","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"農業","answer":["のうぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"farmers,peasants","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"農民","answer":["のうみん"]},
    {"meaning":"to lengthen,to stretch,to reach out,to grow (beard)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"伸ばす","answer":["のばす"]},
    {"meaning":"to stretch,to extend,to make progress,to grow (beard, body height)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"伸びる","answer":["のびる"]},
    {"meaning":"to state,to express,to mention","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"述べる","answer":["のべる"]},
    {"meaning":"to arise,to ascend,to go up","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"昇る","answer":["のぼる"]},
    {"meaning":"ash","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"灰","answer":["はい","あく"]},
    {"meaning":"explosion,detonation,eruption","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"爆発","answer":["ばくはつ"]},
    {"meaning":"skin","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"肌","answer":["はだ"]},
    {"meaning":"counter for birds,counter for rabbits","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"羽","answer":["はね"]},
    {"meaning":"width,breadth","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"幅","answer":["はば"]},
    {"meaning":"to omit,to eliminate,to curtail,to economize","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"省く","answer":["はぶく"]},
    {"meaning":"needle,hand (e.g. clock)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"針","answer":["はり"]},
    {"meaning":"sale,selling,marketing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"販売","answer":["はんばい"]},
    {"meaning":"light","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"灯","answer":["ひ","ともしび"]},
    {"meaning":"damage","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"被害","answer":["ひがい"]},
    {"meaning":"tragedy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"悲劇","answer":["ひげき"]},
    {"meaning":"second (60th min)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"秒","answer":["びょう"]},
    {"meaning":"bottle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"瓶","answer":["びん","かめ"]},
    {"meaning":"garments","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"服装","answer":["ふくそう"]},
    {"meaning":"to hold in the mouth,to bear in mind","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"含む","answer":["ふくむ"]},
    {"meaning":"bag,sack","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"袋","answer":["ふくろ"]},
    {"meaning":"twins,a twin","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"双子","answer":["ふたご"]},
    {"meaning":"again,once more,a second time","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"再び","answer":["ふたたび"]},
    {"meaning":"usually,habitually,ordinarily,always","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"普段","answer":["ふだん"]},
    {"meaning":"writing brush","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"筆","answer":["ふで"]},
    {"meaning":"to touch,to be touched,to touch on a subject,to feel,to violate (law, copyright, etc.),to perceive,t","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"触れる","answer":["ふれる"]},
    {"meaning":"atmosphere (e.g. musical),mood,ambience","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"雰囲気","answer":["ふんいき"]},
    {"meaning":"equilibrium,balance,average,mean","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"平均","answer":["へいきん","ならし"]},
    {"meaning":"to abate,to decrease,to diminish,to shorten","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"減らす","answer":["へらす"]},
    {"meaning":"to decrease (in size or number),to diminish,to abate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"減る","answer":["へる"]},
    {"meaning":"pole,rod,stick","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"棒","answer":["ぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"gem,jewel","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"宝石","answer":["ほうせき"]},
    {"meaning":"abundance,wealth,plenty,bounty","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"豊富","answer":["ほうふ"]},
    {"meaning":"Buddha,merciful person,Buddhist image,the dead","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"仏","answer":["ほとけ","ふつ"]},
    {"meaning":"grandchild","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"孫","answer":["まご"]},
    {"meaning":"festival,feast","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"祭","answer":["まつり"]},
    {"meaning":"circle,full (month),perfection,purity,suffix for ship names","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"丸","answer":["まる"]},
    {"meaning":"round,circular,spherical","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"丸い","answer":["まるい"]},
    {"meaning":"cavity,tooth decay,decayed tooth,caries","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"虫歯","answer":["むしば"]},
    {"meaning":"breast,chest","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"胸","answer":["むね"]},
    {"meaning":"order,command,decree,directive,(software) instruction","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"命令","answer":["めいれい"]},
    {"meaning":"cotton,padding","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"綿","answer":["めん","わた"]},
    {"meaning":"blanket","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"毛布","answer":["もうふ"]},
    {"meaning":"to burn","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"燃える","answer":["もえる"]},
    {"meaning":"roof","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"屋根","answer":["やね"]},
    {"meaning":"courage,bravery,valour,nerve,boldness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"勇気","answer":["ゆうき"]},
    {"meaning":"validity,availability,effectiveness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"有効","answer":["ゆうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"mail,postal service","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"郵便","answer":["ゆうびん"]},
    {"meaning":"floor","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"床","answer":["ゆか","とこ"]},
    {"meaning":"export","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"輸出","answer":["ゆしゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"abundant,wealthy,plentiful,rich","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"豊か","answer":["ゆたか"]},
    {"meaning":"importation,import,introduction","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"輸入","answer":["ゆにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"estimate,budget","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"予算","answer":["よさん"]},
    {"meaning":"prediction,estimation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"予測","answer":["よそく"]},
    {"meaning":"quantity,amount,volume,portion (of food)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"量","answer":["りょう"]},
    {"meaning":"change,money exchange","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"両替","answer":["りょうがえ"]},
    {"meaning":"practice","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"練習","answer":["れんしゅう","れんしゅうする"]},
    {"meaning":"ring,hoop,circle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"輪","answer":["わ","りん"]},
    {"meaning":"bay,gulf,inlet","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"湾","answer":["わん"]},
    {"meaning":"shallow,superficial","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"浅い","answer":["あさい"]},
    {"meaning":"thread","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"糸","answer":["いと"]},
    {"meaning":"to pray","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"祈る","answer":["いのる"]},
    {"meaning":"to plant,to grow","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"植える","answer":["うえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to move house or transfer","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"移る","answer":["うつる"]},
    {"meaning":"arm","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"腕","answer":["うで"]},
    {"meaning":"reverse side","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"裏","answer":["うら"]},
    {"meaning":"branch, twig","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"枝","answer":["えだ"]},
    {"meaning":"congratulation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"お祝い","answer":["おいわい"]},
    {"meaning":"one hundred million","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"億","answer":["おく"]},
    {"meaning":"gift","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"贈り物","answer":["おくりもの"]},
    {"meaning":"a dance","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"踊り","answer":["おどり"]},
    {"meaning":"to dance","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"踊る","answer":["おどる"]},
    {"meaning":"festival","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"お祭り","answer":["おまつり"]},
    {"meaning":"coast","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"海岸","answer":["かいがん"]},
    {"meaning":"to tidy up","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"片付ける","answer":["かたづける"]},
    {"meaning":"section manager","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"課長","answer":["かちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to get dry","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乾く","answer":["かわく"]},
    {"meaning":"simple","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"簡単","answer":["かんたん"]},
    {"meaning":"art,technology,skill","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"技術","answer":["ぎじゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"regulations","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"規則","answer":["きそく"]},
    {"meaning":"competition","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"競争","answer":["きょうそう"]},
    {"meaning":"to compare","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"比べる","answer":["くらべる"]},
    {"meaning":"hair or fur","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"毛","answer":["け"]},
    {"meaning":"outskirts","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"郊外","answer":["こうがい"]},
    {"meaning":"auditorium","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"講堂","answer":["こうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"small, fine","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"細かい","answer":["こまかい"]},
    {"meaning":"slope,hill","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"坂","answer":["さか"]},
    {"meaning":"to touch","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"触る","answer":["さわる"]},
    {"meaning":"island","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"島","answer":["しま"]},
    {"meaning":"judo","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"柔道","answer":["じゅうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"introduction","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"紹介","answer":["しょうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"future,prospects","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"将来","answer":["しょうらい"]},
    {"meaning":"to throw away","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"捨てる","answer":["すてる"]},
    {"meaning":"sand","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"砂","answer":["すな"]},
    {"meaning":"line","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"線","answer":["せん"]},
    {"meaning":"graduation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"卒業","answer":["そつぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"Japanese straw mat","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"畳","answer":["たたみ","じょう"]},
    {"meaning":"blood","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"血","answer":["ち"]},
    {"meaning":"to wrap","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"包む","answer":["つつむ","くるむ"]},
    {"meaning":"glove","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"手袋","answer":["てぶくろ"]},
    {"meaning":"temple","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"寺","answer":["てら"]},
    {"meaning":"electric light","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"電灯","answer":["でんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"to reach","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"届ける","answer":["とどける"]},
    {"meaning":"to lodge at","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"泊まる","answer":["とまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to exchange","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"取り替える","answer":["とりかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"thief","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"泥棒","answer":["どろぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"to paint,to plaster","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"塗る","answer":["ぬる"]},
    {"meaning":"to change between buses or trains","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乗り換える","answer":["のりかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"double","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"倍","answer":["ばい"]},
    {"meaning":"woods,forester","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"林","answer":["はやし"]},
    {"meaning":"after a long time","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"久しぶり","answer":["ひさしぶり"]},
    {"meaning":"to pick up,to gather","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"拾う","answer":["ひろう"]},
    {"meaning":"complexity,complication","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"複雑","answer":["ふくざつ"]},
    {"meaning":"revision","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"復習","answer":["ふくしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"usually, or a train that stops at every station","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"普通","answer":["ふつう"]},
    {"meaning":"Japanese bedding, futon","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"布団","answer":["ふとん"]},
    {"meaning":"ship","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"舟","answer":["ふね"]},
    {"meaning":"trade","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"貿易","answer":["ぼうえき"]},
    {"meaning":"law","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"法律","answer":["ほうりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"star","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"星","answer":["ほし"]},
    {"meaning":"surroundings","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"周り","answer":["まわり"]},
    {"meaning":"lake","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"湖","answer":["みずうみ"]},
    {"meaning":"insect","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"虫","answer":["むし"]},
    {"meaning":"(polite) to eat","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"召し上がる","answer":["めしあがる"]},
    {"meaning":"rare","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"珍しい","answer":["めずらしい"]},
    {"meaning":"cotton","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"木綿","answer":["もめん","きわた"]},
    {"meaning":"forest","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"森","answer":["もり"]},
    {"meaning":"to bake,to grill","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"焼く","answer":["やく"]},
    {"meaning":"to burn,to be roasted","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"焼ける","answer":["やける"]},
    {"meaning":"soft","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"柔らかい","answer":["やわらかい"]},
    {"meaning":"hot water","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"湯","answer":["ゆ"]},
    {"meaning":"finger ring","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"指輪","answer":["ゆびわ"]},
    {"meaning":"to get dirty","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"汚れる","answer":["よごれる","けがれる"]},
    {"meaning":"history","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"歴史","answer":["れきし"]},
    {"meaning":"contact","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"連絡","answer":["れんらく"]},
    {"meaning":"to boil,to heat","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"沸かす","answer":["わかす"]},
    {"meaning":"to boil, to grow hot,to get excited","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"沸く","answer":["わく"]},
    {"meaning":"kind, deep, thick","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"厚い","answer":["あつい"]},
    {"meaning":"sweet","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"甘い","answer":["あまい","うまい"]},
    {"meaning":"pond","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"池","answer":["いけ"]},
    {"meaning":"thin,weak","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"薄い","answer":["うすい"]},
    {"meaning":"great number of people","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"大勢","answer":["おおぜい"]},
    {"meaning":"sweets, candy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"お菓子","answer":["おかし"]},
    {"meaning":"(honorable) wife","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"奥さん","answer":["おくさん"]},
    {"meaning":"plate, dish","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"お皿","answer":["おさら"]},
    {"meaning":"a vase","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"花瓶","answer":["かびん"]},
    {"meaning":"Light","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"軽い","answer":["かるい"]},
    {"meaning":"Dirty","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"汚い","answer":["きたない"]},
    {"meaning":"coffee lounge","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"喫茶店","answer":["きっさてん"]},
    {"meaning":"Ticket","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"切符","answer":["きっぷ"]},
    {"meaning":"Milk","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"牛乳","answer":["ぎゅうにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"cloudy weather","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"曇り","answer":["くもり"]},
    {"meaning":"to become cloudy, to become dim","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"曇る","answer":["くもる"]},
    {"meaning":"black tea","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"紅茶","answer":["こうちゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"Wallet","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"財布","answer":["さいふ"]},
    {"meaning":"to bloom","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"咲く","answer":["さく"]},
    {"meaning":"Magazine","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"雑誌","answer":["ざっし"]},
    {"meaning":"Salt","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"塩","answer":["しお","えん"]},
    {"meaning":"Refreshing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"涼しい","answer":["すずしい"]},
    {"meaning":"Washing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"洗濯","answer":["せんたく"]},
    {"meaning":"egg","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"卵","answer":["たまご"]},
    {"meaning":"underground train","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"地下鉄","answer":["ちかてつ"]},
    {"meaning":"desk","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"机","answer":["つくえ"]},
    {"meaning":"Japanese style door","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"戸","answer":["と","こ"]},
    {"meaning":"to line up,to stand in a line","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"並ぶ","answer":["ならぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"to line up,to set up","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"並べる","answer":["ならべる"]},
    {"meaning":"luggage","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"荷物","answer":["にもつ"]},
    {"meaning":"luke warm","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"温い","answer":["ぬるい"]},
    {"meaning":"ashtray","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"灰皿","answer":["はいざら","はいさら"]},
    {"meaning":"bridge","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"橋","answer":["はし"]},
    {"meaning":"short,low","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"低い","answer":["ひくい"]},
    {"meaning":"envelope","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"封筒","answer":["ふうとう"]},
    {"meaning":"sentence,text","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"文章","answer":["ぶんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"area","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"辺","answer":["へん"]},
    {"meaning":"hat","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"帽子","answer":["ぼうし"]},
    {"meaning":"thin","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"細い","answer":["ほそい"]},
    {"meaning":"fountain pen","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"万年筆","answer":["まんねんひつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to brush teeth, to polish","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"磨く","answer":["みがく"]},
    {"meaning":"short","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"短い","answer":["みじかい"]},
    {"meaning":"green","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"緑","answer":["みどり"]},
    {"meaning":"village","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"村","answer":["むら"]},
    {"meaning":"gate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"門","answer":["もん","かど"]},
    {"meaning":"vegetable","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"野菜","answer":["やさい"]},
    {"meaning":"post office","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"郵便局","answer":["ゆうびんきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"weak","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"弱い","answer":["よわい"]},
    {"meaning":"refrigerator","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"冷蔵庫","answer":["れいぞうこ"]}
  ]}

